<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>family on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/categories/family/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in family on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://libmb.github.io/categories/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>VISITORS</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning we cleaned up around the house- then headed to the airport to meet Steph &amp;amp; Geoff!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/airport.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sign&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, Steph brought supplies to restock our Wegmans necessities! &lt;em&gt;the best!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/wegmans.png&#34; alt=&#34;Food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were so excited to have guests, and there were so many places we wanted to take them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday evening we headed over to Galvanize, so I could show all three around my new school. We met an instructor and one of my cohort peers who was getting some work in. Zac and Geoff also squeezed in a game of ping pong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gschool.png&#34; alt=&#34;Galvanize&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we headed over to McLoughlins for a drink before going to Zengo for dinner with Zac and Stephs cousin, Danielle and her boyfriend Tim. After, we were still a little hungry, so we walked up to Littleman for some ice cream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/littleman.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;little man&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday we went to Eldora for a day of skiing/snowboarding. It was a pretty nice day, we were actually really warm but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to trek back to the car to ditch our jackets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/eldora.png&#34; alt=&#34;skiing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday night we headed out. First we stopped at Avanti for drinks and food. Then we went all the way to Larimer where we got a drink and took in the gorgeous view that is Larimer at nighttime. On the way home, we stopped by Rocket Fizz because its fun to browse candies that were around during our childhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/avanti_lar.png&#34; alt=&#34;avanti and larimer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday we went to the Botanic Gardens. It was SCFD Free day! It was free, and I am obsessed with the Gardens so it was a no brainer. Unfortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s winter, and so everything is dead. It was a little lackluster but the rainforest was still pretty awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gardens.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;botanic gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next we drove out to Boulder to do some walking along Pearl St. It was cold in the wind, but the sun was nice. We stopped for food and had the worst service.. but overall it was a nice day out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday night we headed to the hockey game!!!! And when we got there, it was empty! Ha, Zac had purchased tickets for a Tuesday game, thinking it was Monday. Instead we just walked over to PublicSchool303 for drinks and dinner. An old friend was in town, so she stopped by too and it was nice to catch up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/nothockey.png&#34; alt=&#34;not hockey&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday while I was in class, everyone went up to Red Rocks to explore. After class, I met everyone at Denver Beer Co, and we headed to the ACTUAL hockey game! The Avalanche are literally the worst team in the NHL, but sports are fun so it was worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/hockey.png&#34; alt=&#34;hockey&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday morning Steph joined me at the gym!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym buddy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday night Zac had gotten Steph and Geoff a hotel in Cherry Creek so they could have a night of vacation together! We went grocery shopping and did laundry&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday while I was in class, the group went to a brewery and an arcade. After, we went to Bones for dinner. It was a great meal, and the restaurant is nice and intimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/bones.png&#34; alt=&#34;bones dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was our LAST DAY. While I was in class Zac, Steph and Geoff headed to Keystone for some AWESOME skiing/snowboarding and I&amp;rsquo;m jealous! I would have loved to go, but i&amp;rsquo;ll get to next time. When I got home from school everyone was really tired and apparently the altitude was putting some stress on them. Zac stayed home while the three of us went down the road to My Brothers Bar for some dinner. It was ok.. but we were really hungry so it worked!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning, before leaving, we went and grabbed brunch at Carbon. We will miss them so much, but it was a GREAT week and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see them again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/carbon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;carbon brunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/bye.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge pic&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>