<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shelter&#39;s House </title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <author></author>
    <rights>(C) 2017</rights>
    <updated>2017-01-26 17:00:00 &#43;0900 &#43;0900</updated>

    
      
        <item>
          <title>Code Catchup</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_26/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 17:00:00 &#43;0900</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_26/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Since moving to Denver in July, I have been working hard to learn how to code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_26/codewars.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;codewars&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Way back in middle school, I ran a website. It was for quotes- which I am sure were not properly cited, but the site was cool, the cursor had a tail, and it was definitely pink. I was self taught. After school, I would come home and sit at the computer for hours trying to figure out how the code worked. How I could pick it apart and put it together. Slowly figuring out how I could get my site to do something new. I loved it. Then, the quote trend passed, and I moved away from that side of learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my first paraprofessional role, I found myself leading programs for kids. One of the first was a program using Scratch. I loved it. I had so much fun with those kids, and they were so creative. I realized that I was still really interested in learning how to code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_26/scratch1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;scratch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I interviewed for a new position. The interviewer asked what I wanted to learn for myself in the next year- what were my personal goals? In response, I said I wanted to learn how to code. That I had wanted to, and that it would be a good thing to work on. OF COURSE, I really had no time. I signed up for a few online classes.. but never practiced enough to retain anything I was learning. I even joined the mailing list for Girls Who Code in Syracuse, but never made it to a class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in June, when we decided to make the move to Denver, I was taking Rex for a walk. I found myself once again thinking,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I would really love to learn web development. Maybe, in like 10 years, I&amp;rsquo;ll have the time to learn it and it can be a second career&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, I realized, why wait? Why wait to learn, what I have already been waiting to learn? So, I got home, and brought it up with Zac. Now, I have an amazingly supportive husband. He was all for it, and he&amp;rsquo;s supported me every step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_26/deskweek.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;weekday&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_26/deskwknd.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;weekend&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we moved, and almost every day since August, I have been coding. Learning through Codeacademy, Udacity and Codewars. On the weekends, Zac and I will pair up and work on projects together. All along, I have been working to be good enough to apply for a bootcamp. This month, I applied. I interviewed. I was accepted. AND in just over two weeks I will be starting the immersive web development program at Galvanize Platte! I&amp;rsquo;M SO EXCITED.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_26/rexsnout.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;scratch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do want to mention right now that I still LOVE library science. It is my goal to combine all of the skills I have with the skills I&amp;rsquo;ll learn.  I have zero regrets when it comes to the decisions I&amp;rsquo;ve made this far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_26/macbookpro.png&#34; alt=&#34;new computer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I&amp;rsquo;m prepping for the course. It&amp;rsquo;s intensive, so I&amp;rsquo;m trying to prepare myself ahead of time. Adjusting my sleep schedule, hitting the gym early, spending time with meal plans! I&amp;rsquo;m also still learning- and getting use to my new Macbook Pro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_26/rollingmacs.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pair&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;s going to be challenging, but let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, I love a good challenge. I love learning. I love being busy. And, I&amp;rsquo;m hecka excited. I can hardly wait&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Fight Gone Bad</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_19/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_19/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It takes 21 days to make a habit, and I&amp;rsquo;m on day 19 of Tone It Up! That&amp;rsquo;s 2 days from a habit? AND 2 days since &amp;ldquo;Ditch Day&amp;rdquo;. This week I&amp;rsquo;m feeling great again. Last week I had some ups and downs-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_spotify.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;playlist&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, helpful tool of the week: CARDIO PLAYLIST ON SPOTIFY.
Seriously love this list so much. After I finished my last audiobook, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get into the next one I picked. I was only a few days away from a new Audible credit, so I decided to wait it out and listen to some music (&amp;amp; catch some TV like NFL GAME DAY and a movie here or there). I have my new credit, and love my new book- but I only listen to it during cardio. Ironically, the rest of the time, I&amp;rsquo;m moving to the Cardio Playlist! If you&amp;rsquo;re into high octane music, give it a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_tv.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tv&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I learned last week is that I NEED TO EAT. I was so busy- I was jumping from one thing to the next and not prioritizing all 5 meals. So, I&amp;rsquo;d skip one, or two, in a day. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t feel hungry, until bed time. At that point, I knew I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to eat anything. I&amp;rsquo;m trying REALLY hard not to eat anything after 7pm. So, I went to bed hungry. This was a HUGE MISTAKE. With the workouts, cardio and yoga I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing- I need food! Power! Energy! (Also, everyone needs food, and you should never go to bed hungry). I ended up crashing last week- and took some long naps. Then I started keeping up with meals. Even if I had to combine a M2 and M3, or a M4 and M5. I ate all the food in the plan. And you know what- I didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed hungry, and I have so much energy. So, EAT! It&amp;rsquo;s part of taking care of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_food.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eating aside, I also somehow hurt my leg this past weekend. Just a strained muscle- but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to move it into an injury- so while I&amp;rsquo;ve kept up on all workouts, I have been going just a little bit easier on my cardio (little less resistance, a few less strides/minute). It already feels better and I think I&amp;rsquo;ll kick cardio back up a notch in a day or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym window&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for workouts, I never purchased the workout videos from Tone It Up. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;ve been creating my own circuits. The ability to create these, well, I give all of the credit to Crossfit! Oh- a 22 minute video doing legs and shoulders? I&amp;rsquo;ll throw together an EMOM. Or a METCON. Or, my absolute fav, Fight Gone Bad Style. Today there was an Arms and Abs video I don&amp;rsquo;t have- so I threw together this FGB style workout: crunches, plank, sit ups, push ups, arm circles, break, dumbbell side bend, med ball chopper, farm carry, balance point crunches, break. The flow feels really productive- and you can do anything for 1 minute!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_FGB.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;workout&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Crossfit- I do miss it. I miss it most on days when the plan calls for something like deadlifts, and I&amp;rsquo;m like- where my Olympic Weights at? Haha. I can only do so much with 12 lb dumbbells&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took a little time off from Yoga this week- due to my leg, but I did make one great class on a sunny morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;yoga&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight, Zac gets home- and he&amp;rsquo;s off travel next week. I&amp;rsquo;ll be happy to have my work out partner back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_bud.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Zac&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Midway through week 4, I love the plan. My water intake is 100% and my eating is great. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_day.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;day&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>The movies, Lax and drinks!!</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_17/</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 17:00:00 &#43;0900</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_17/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s only been 9 days since my last post, and I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s been 9 days! After a slow start to last week, the second half and weekend flew by! I think this post will be a long one&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_indy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog cuddles&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(How great is that sweatshirt thought? It&amp;rsquo;s IndyBrand and I want ALL THE THINGS).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday morning Zac was off to LA for work! Rex and I went for a great walk. The sun was out, and after I felt pretty engergized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_riverfront.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;walk riverfront&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the day I finished up some work on the computer. That night, Shadow hunters aired and I was SO excited about it. So, after yoga, Rex and I settled in for a great show. About half way through Zac called, and I was whispering. He asked what was wrong- Oh, nothing, just in the middle of a show- ya know? Haha but it was practically over so we still caught up on his first day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday was GORGEOUS! I woke up and went to Yoga with one of my favorite teachers. After, I grabbed a lavender honey latte at Carbon Beverage. It was SO GOOD. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get anything to eat, but look at the picture- I will NEED to go back and get a huge cinnamon bun someday (with Zac, to help).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_carbon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;carbon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rex and I sat in the sun on our patio. It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect area- you&amp;rsquo;re totally blocked from the wind, but have full sun access! I was hot sitting in my tank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_out1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunny day&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_out2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunny day&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday I woke up and decided to run some errands. We had some gift cards from Christmas- and that is my favorite way to shop! First I headed to Barnes and Noble- where I perused the shelves, tables, and displays before buying the two books I knew I was going to buy (but, as always, I was tempted). I also added a bunch of books to my Goodreads to-read section. Sighs. I bought the Handmaid&amp;rsquo;s Tale, which I don&amp;rsquo;t own and need to re-read, and Bridget Jones&amp;rsquo;s Diary- which I have never read! Honest: I have high expectations there. We&amp;rsquo;ll see when I get around to them. All my library holds came in at the same time, so prioritizing is an issue-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next stop was literally right next door, Pier One. I use to buy wine glasses there EVERY YEAR. Seriously, they have these beautiful huge goblet like glasses (but more regular size than toyish)&amp;hellip; with the perfect thin glass lip. Every year I would break at least 2, and replace them after Christmas. Until last year, when I bought a bunch of stainless steel (not as great, but still pretty great with the added bonus of not breaking into my disposal).  So this year, I found a soft fluffy pillow and a candle. Trying to be minimal means that I look for things that don&amp;rsquo;t take up too much space, and are functional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_shopping.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;shopping&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I was in the area- I also stopped at Ikea. I needed some food storage containers, and you can&amp;rsquo;t beat their prices. I also stumbled upon a blanket/pillow cover display and got a few things to change up what I had on the couch (going along with the Pier 1 pillow).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_couch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;couch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, in the afternoon- I hit a wall. Just totally completely exhausted! I took a really long nap with my new pillow and blanket. So that was great. It was also still really nice out- so for the third day in a row, I was able to open the windows and get some fresh air in the apartment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_window.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday night I went to an info session at Turing. (AND I HAVE SO MUCH NEWS FOR THAT WORLD- but that&amp;rsquo;ll come in a later post). For now, just know that I got to wear my new shoes that I got for Christmas! Zac&amp;rsquo;s sister gave them to me and I love them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_shoes.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before Zac got home on Thursday night I headed to Happy Hour at Avanti&amp;rsquo;s with a friend. She invited a huge group, and everyone brought more people. There ended up being like 20-25 of us, and everyone was really great. Before, every time we went to Avanti, I would look at the bar area thinking &amp;lsquo;I need to get here some night&amp;rsquo;, and it was definitely what I expected. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to take Zac there some time for drinks- and to introduce him to some of the people I met that night!  When Zac got on the train, I walked the two blocks home. I was so busy talking, I got NO pictures. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to work on that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Friday, I got the most unexpected and perfectly timed box ever. My dear friend, who I admire and am so lucky to know, sent me a holiday/care package. We&amp;rsquo;ve been talking a lot about life. Actually, we always do, and always will. I&amp;rsquo;m lucky to know her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_gift1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gift&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_gift2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gift&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac was back from LA, so in the morning we took Rex for a walk and grabbed coffee at ink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_ink.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ink&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday I watched a couple episodes of Lemony Snicket- while doing some work. After Zac got off work- we FINALLY went and saw Rogue One! IT WAS GREAT. We had tried to go for weeks, but the AMC Flatiron was totally sold out. I&amp;rsquo;m a sucker for the lay down movie theater, so we kept waiting. We loved it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we went for a long walk. It was nice outside, but not great. We walked to a few different areas we hadn&amp;rsquo;t explored yet, so that was nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_train.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gift&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That night, we had tickets to the Mammoth game! We use to love going to lax games in Buffalo, and were pretty excited to have a team here in Denver. First we stopped for drinks and apps at a place called Public School 303. It was adorable! Decorated for school- they have flash cards on the walls, and menus that look like composition notebooks. Plus, the food and drinks (&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; liter of wine on happy hour!) were fantastic. The wings reminded me a place my brother and I went as kids- they had the BEST wings, so that&amp;rsquo;s a high compliment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_ps303.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;public school&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_ps3032.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;public school&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we walked to the game and had so much fun! I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to go again. It was a really close game too- we won.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_pc.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pepsi center&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_lax.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;mammoth&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday was FOOTBALL DAY. The games were CRAZY! I am stoked that the Steelers won, and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to cheer them on this weekend (and every other day, GO STEELERS!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_dog_nap.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rest of the weekend was filled in with dog cuddles, walks, and trips to the gym. We also started watching The Man at High Castle, and I think that&amp;rsquo;s going to be a great show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, I&amp;rsquo;ll wrap up.. I have a delicious smelling coconut lemon curry to go eat. Exciting news coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_17/2017_01_17_lcsoup.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Tone it Up!</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_10/</link>
          <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_10/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been just over a week since I started Tone It Up! I&amp;rsquo;ve used the nutrition plan for Fit Girls a few times the past couple years, and while I loved the food, I started to get sick of the same recipes. It was time to switch things up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, I&amp;rsquo;m loving the meals- and the daily workouts are definitely doable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One dinner I love is Lentil Butternut Squash Soup. I really did not think I would enjoy this.. but I really like everything about it. It has just the right amount of spice and texture. I actually already made it a second time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_bns.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also finally tried smoothie bowls. The first time, I used a fresh banana because I hadn&amp;rsquo;t had time to freeze them yet- and without realizing the difference it makes, I was really confused as to why people make smoothie bowls. I actually just grabbed a straw to drink it. The next day, I decided to try again, and the frozen banana made all the difference. I LOVE this breakfast. It&amp;rsquo;s almost as great as eating frozen yogurt with great toppings. Almost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_bowl.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac and I have been hitting the gym on his lunch break. It&amp;rsquo;s so great to have a gym partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A serious goal for 2017 is to improve my double unders. I mean, I only string together a max of 6, so there is a lot of room for improvement. Until then, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep beating myself up. Literally, whip marks on my legs, arms and sometimes I&amp;rsquo;ll need to ice a knuckle or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_rope.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;double&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every workout has been followed by a smoothie.. and I love, love, LOVE smoothies. I drink mine in like 2 minutes, while Zac takes a while- you know, drinking at a normal pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_smoothie.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;smoothie&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, Kindness Yoga is also holding a January Challenge. My goal is to get to 15 classes this month. I went to 4 classes last week, and they make such a huge difference in how I feel. It&amp;rsquo;s been hard- I prioritize it after my workout for the day, and sometimes I can hardly hold myself up because my muscles are so tired. Still worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Starting off 2017!</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_08/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_08/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Hope everyone has had a great start to the year! It was a cold week here in Denver, but we had a great week nonetheless. I have been re-watching Downton Abbey&amp;ndash; on Monday I realized I could stream Amazon Video through the XBox, and I am THRILLED. Truth is, I missed the last season, and I need to watch! I&amp;rsquo;ve kept them playing pretty much all day while I work on different CodeAcademy/Computer Projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_comp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;downton&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of computer projects&amp;mdash; on Wednesday I lured a friend out for drinks so that I could question her about WebDev and local programs. She was an awesome source of information (as well as an awesome person)- and I have a lot to consider. Wednesday this coming week I am attending an info session at Turing School, and then I&amp;rsquo;ll start applying and see what happens. It might take a few tries, but I am loving everything I&amp;rsquo;m learning, and I am ready to move forward at a faster pace!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday night we went to the Botanic Gardens for an Off The Clock event. The same friend above invited us, and we meet another couple there. It was a fun little night. I just LOVE walking around the gardens. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for summer- I think I&amp;rsquo;ll just go and sit a couple days a week- because. It also makes me wish I could grow things, but let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, keeping plants alive is not my strong suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_gardens.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we were planning on snowboarding, but were just too sore to make it up. Instead, we slept in and took care of some things around the apartment. In the morning, we walked to Panera Bread to get a loaf (and a Caramel Latte) to go with our bean-less Chili. I made a large batch in December and froze portions for trips to the mountain. I had already thawed one, so chili for lunch it was! Rexy loved the walk- and he gets more compliments, laughs and smiles when he wears his boots. Seriously, no one is immune to the cuteness that is dog boots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_panera.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Panera&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got home, it was straight to the paw-wash! Of course, he was filthy, and overjoyed by the prospect of being hosed down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_dogbath.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday afternoon I finished up another jar of Justin&amp;rsquo;s Almond Butter. I have been drinking SO MANY smoothies, and eating so many smoothie bowls, that I needed a cost effective option. I mentioned this to Zac, and an hour later, he was in the kitchen whipping up a batch of his first ever homemade PB! Guys- ITS AMAZING. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for peanuts we can buy in bulk&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_pb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, it was FOOTBALL DAY. How about them Steelers? Gosh I am so excited about this post season. After the Steelers game, I headed to the gym- where I caught most of the Packers Giants game, and the Golden Globes Red Carpet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_elip.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;TV&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it was time for Restorative Yoga at Kindness. I love this weekly class- its the perfect way to wrap up a week! It was a particularly great class- and afterwards, Zac met me with Rex to walk home. Always the gentleman, he carries my Yoga mat like a pro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s 2017 already. I will say, that being back in Denver finally feels like home and not just a vacation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_denver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Monthly Reads</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_05/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_05/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;In December I finished 11 books. That&amp;rsquo;s CRAZY! I think that I associate the holiday season with curling up with a book.. and therefore take every opportunity to do so!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The books:
  The Graveyard Book Vol 1,&lt;br /&gt;
  The Graveyard Book Vol 2,&lt;br /&gt;
  Winter Stroll,
  Winter Storms,
  Eligible,
  Crooked Kingdom,
  The Woman in Cabin 10,
  All The Time in the World,
  A Man Called Ove,
  Paper Princess&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_GYB.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Graveyard&#34; /&gt;
The Graveyard Book by Neil Gaiman, and Craig P. Russell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graveyard Book volumes were beautiful. I always wanted to get to this book- and when a friend tagged the graphic novel in her banned books post, it brought them up to the top of my list. I actually had hoped to read them in time for Halloween- but other library loans were ending and it got side tracked until December. I digresss.. This was a wonderful story- I love all the characters, and the different ways you can interpret the story itself. &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars | &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_Stroll.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;stroll&#34; /&gt;
Winter Stroll(Winter 2) by Elin Hilderbrand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked up the first book in this series, Winter Street, while I was visiting my family for Thanksgiving. The book was sitting on my Aunts coffee table, and I was instantly grabbed by the cover- the beautiful red door, and I wanted a holiday read. I finished it in just over a day, and really enjoyed reading it. Then I had to pick up this one. &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_storm.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;storm&#34; /&gt;
Winter Storms(Winter 3) by Elin Hilderbrand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to summarize these books individually, because they really form a cohesive story. There are ups, there are downs. It shows how a family loves, grieves, and continues to move through life. A great holiday series. &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_eligible.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;eligible&#34; /&gt;
Eligible: A Modern Retelling of Pride and Prejudice by Curtis Sittenfeld&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Book club book! Alright, so I moved in July- but I miss my book club! They keep me in loop with what they are reading, and I try to read them even if I&amp;rsquo;m not there for the fantastic conversation and great food/drinks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, I needed to read this. I WILL READ ANY FORM OF PRIDE AND PREJUDICE EVER. So, did I like this book? YES. I loved it. ITS P&amp;amp;P! In the beginning I was a little irritated by the &amp;ldquo;modern&amp;rdquo; aspect, but after a few chapters I fell into the new rhythm and I honestly like what they did with the characters. I&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping this one. &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars (bias)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_crooked.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;crooked&#34; /&gt;
Crooked Kingdom by Leigh Bardugo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kaz and his crew are BA. Seriously. It makes me want to climb over roofs and scheme! This book, like the first, will keep you on your toes. Not even you will know what Kaz is up to, until he wants you to know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without giving spoilers, I will say that this final book tied into the Grishaverse and I was SO pleasantly surprised by that! &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_cabin10.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cabin&#34; /&gt;
The Woman in Cabin 10 by Ruth Ware&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first few chapters, I was really concerned that this book would be too much like Girl on the Train (which was a great book, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to read the same story)..(unless its p&amp;amp;p). It wasn&amp;rsquo;t! A tale all of its own. I was surprised, I think the ending was brilliant, and I recommend! &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_attitw.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;time&#34; /&gt;
All the Time in the World by Caroline Angell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book was so heart breaking and uplifting at the same time. Not uplifting in a everything turns out perfect way, but in a life goes on way. I cannot imagine the burden of the loss these characters face, and yet, I feel like Angell did a wonderful job of showing us different aspects of being human and helped me relate to the characters. &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_ove.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ove&#34; /&gt;
A Man Called Ove by Fredrik Backman&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;READ THIS BOOK! So, three chapters into this book I loved Ove. 5 Chapters in I said it would be one of the best books I read in 2016. By the end, it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite books ever. Ove is reminiscent of Carl Fredricksen from the movie UP and has a bit of Gran Torino to it as well. One page, Ove will have you laughing, and the next he&amp;rsquo;ll have you in tears. I think that I learned something from Ove, and that we can always use a new prespective. &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, I read Paper Princess by Erin Watt; I don&amp;rsquo;t have a picture of this book, and I gave it zero stars on Goodreads. Why? Because I was so shocked by the book that I was not ready to process it. I&amp;rsquo;m still not, so I&amp;rsquo;ll hold off on that. Here is what I will say: The main character is a girl in high school. She meets a boy and it becomes more of an erotic genre than what I had expected- I expected a YA book! Now, I see people saying this is NA&amp;ndash; I DO NOT AGREE. NA should bridge the gap of teen and adult- but if I was doing Readers Advisory for New Adult, I would NOT include this as an option (and if you are, perhaps you should mention the main theme). Hey, as far as erotic novels go- it was okay. But NA? No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stars are based on what I gave the book on Goodreads. However, you should know that I am particularly stingy with my 5 stars. Also, I don&amp;rsquo;t read bad books. As in, I might start a book, and if I don&amp;rsquo;t like it, I put it down. Life is too short to read bad books.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Holiday Travel</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_01/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_01/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It has been a crazy week, but it was full of family, friends and ended with the start of the New Year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/chrismukka.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chrismukkah&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Christmas Eve we drove up to Rochester to see my Aunt and cousins. My Aunt throws a &amp;ldquo;Chrismukkah&amp;rdquo; party, and her best friend brings her two adorable girls, her husband, and their parents. It was great to see them all again- to practice my lazy ASL and get an insight to RSL (The grandparents speak RSL and know hardly any ASL!). It was a lot of fun, it&amp;rsquo;s always crazy to see how fast those kids grow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/snap.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chrismukkah&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christmas day we spent with Zac&amp;rsquo;s family (and OF COURSE, Cheered on the STEELRS!). It was a really great day, and it was such a wonderful time of year to catch up with everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were in town we got to visit some new local places- a brewery, a cider mill and a coffee place (which we ended up at more than once). Everything we had was awesome, and I hope these local businesses are really successful this year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/drinks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drinks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also stopped at Wegmans, so that I could get my fill of Wegmans-brand products. Call me crazy, but the White Shells Mac &amp;amp; Cheese is unlike any other brand. We actually got flagged going through airport security because I stuck 12 boxes in Zac&amp;rsquo;s carry on&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of getting home- thankfully Zac is a seasoned flier now! We arrived at the airport and it was completely closed down for suspicious activity. Zac called the nearest airport, and got us out from there. Luckily we had great family members driving us all around!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/airport.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;airport&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We made it home late Thursday, and were greeted Friday by a BEAUTIFUL Denver Winter day. It was 60 degrees! So, after picking up Rex, we took a walk to Avanti&amp;rsquo;s for lunch. We love it there. So much to choose from, and it all tastes so fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/denver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;denver&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To end the year, we ended up dog sitting for a dog friend. Leo was a sweet addition to the evening, and we spent some time cuddling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/nye.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dogs&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that you had a great holiday season! HAPPY 2017!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/rexey.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    

  </channel>
</rss>
