<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finding Shelter </title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/index.xml</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <author></author>
    <rights>(C) 2017</rights>
    <updated>2017-01-09 16:11:58 &#43;0530 &#43;0530</updated>

    
      
        <item>
          <title>Tone it Up!</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_10/</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_10/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been just over a week since I started Tone It Up! I&amp;rsquo;ve used the nutrition plan for Fit Girls a few times the past couple years, and while I loved the food, I started to get sick of the same recipes. It was time to switch things up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, I&amp;rsquo;m loving the meals- and the daily workouts are definitely doable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One dinner I love is Lentil Butternut Squash Soup. I really did not think I would enjoy this.. but I really like everything about it. It has just the right amount of spice and texture. I actually already made it a second time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_10_bns.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also finally tried smoothie bowls. The first time, I used a fresh banana because I hadn&amp;rsquo;t had time to freeze them yet- and without realizing the difference it makes, I was really confused as to why people make smoothie bowls. I actually just grabbed a straw to drink it. The next day, I decided to try again, and the frozen banana made all the difference. I LOVE this breakfast. It&amp;rsquo;s almost as great as eating frozen yogurt with great toppings. Almost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_10_bowl.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac and I have been hitting the gym on his lunch break. It&amp;rsquo;s so great to have a gym partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_10_gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A serious goal for 2017 is to improve my double unders. I mean, I only string together a max of 6, so there is a lot of room for improvement. Until then, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep beating myself up. Literally, whip marks on my legs, arms and sometimes I&amp;rsquo;ll need to ice a knuckle or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_10_rope.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;double&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every workout has been followed by a smoothie.. and I love, love, LOVE smoothies. I drink mine in like 2 minutes, while Zac takes a while- you know, drinking at a normal pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_10_smoothie.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;smoothie&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, Kindness Yoga is also holding a January Challenge. My goal is to get to 15 classes this month. I went to 4 classes last week, and they make such a huge difference in how I feel. It&amp;rsquo;s been hard- I prioritize it after my workout for the day, and sometimes I can hardly hold myself up because my muscles are so tired. Still worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_10_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Starting off 2017!</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_08/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_08/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Hope everyone has had a great start to the year! It was a cold week here in Denver, but we had a great week nonetheless. I have been re-watching Downton Abbey&amp;ndash; on Monday I realized I could stream Amazon Video through the XBox, and I am THRILLED. Truth is, I missed the last season, and I need to watch! I&amp;rsquo;ve kept them playing pretty much all day while I work on different CodeAcademy/Computer Projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_08_comp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;downton&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of computer projects&amp;mdash; on Wednesday I lured a friend out for drinks so that I could question her about WebDev and local programs. She was an awesome source of information (as well as an awesome person)- and I have a lot to consider. Wednesday this coming week I am attending an info session at Turing School, and then I&amp;rsquo;ll start applying and see what happens. It might take a few tries, but I am loving everything I&amp;rsquo;m learning, and I am ready to move forward at a faster pace!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday night we went to the Botanic Gardens for an Off The Clock event. The same friend above invited us, and we meet another couple there. It was a fun little night. I just LOVE walking around the gardens. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for summer- I think I&amp;rsquo;ll just go and sit a couple days a week- because. It also makes me wish I could grow things, but let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, keeping plants alive is not my strong suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_08_gardens.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we were planning on snowboarding, but were just too sore to make it up. Instead, we slept in and took care of some things around the apartment. In the morning, we walked to Panera Bread to get a loaf (and a Caramel Latte) to go with our bean-less Chili. I made a large batch in December and froze portions for trips to the mountain. I had already thawed one, so chili for lunch it was! Rexy loved the walk- and he gets more compliments, laughs and smiles when he wears his boots. Seriously, no one is immune to the cuteness that is dog boots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_08_panera.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Panera&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got home, it was straight to the paw-wash! Of course, he was filthy, and overjoyed by the prospect of being hosed down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_08_dogbath.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday afternoon I finished up another jar of Justin&amp;rsquo;s Almond Butter. I have been drinking SO MANY smoothies, and eating so many smoothie bowls, that I needed a cost effective option. I mentioned this to Zac, and an hour later, he was in the kitchen whipping up a batch of his first ever homemade PB! Guys- ITS AMAZING. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for peanuts we can buy in bulk&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_08_pb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, it was FOOTBALL DAY. How about them Steelers? Gosh I am so excited about this post season. After the Steelers game, I headed to the gym- where I caught most of the Packers Giants game, and the Golden Globes Red Carpet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_10_elip.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;TV&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it was time for Restorative Yoga at Kindness. I love this weekly class- its the perfect way to wrap up a week! It was a particularly great class- and afterwards, Zac met me with Rex to walk home. Always the gentleman, he carries my Yoga mat like a pro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_08_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s 2017 already. I will say, that being back in Denver finally feels like home and not just a vacation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_08_denver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Monthly Reads</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_05/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_05/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;In December I finished 11 books. That&amp;rsquo;s CRAZY! I think that I associate the holiday season with curling up with a book.. and therefore take every opportunity to do so!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The books:
  The Graveyard Book Vol 1
  The Graveyard Book Vol 2
  Winter Stroll
  Winter Storms
  Eligible
  Crooked Kingdom
  The Woman in Cabin 10
  All The Time in the World
  A Man Called Ove
  Paper Princess&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016_12_reads_GYB.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Graveyard&#34; /&gt;
The Graveyard Book by Neil Gaiman, and Craig P. Russell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graveyard Book volumes were beautiful. I always wanted to get to this book- and when a friend tagged the graphic novel in her banned books post, it brought them up to the top of my list. I actually had hoped to read them in time for Halloween- but other library loans were ending and it got side tracked until December. I digresss.. This was a wonderful story- I love all the characters, and the different ways you can interpret the story itself. &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars | &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016_12_reads_Stroll.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;stroll&#34; /&gt;
Winter Stroll(Winter 2) by Elin Hilderbrand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked up the first book in this series, Winter Street, while I was visiting my family for Thanksgiving. The book was sitting on my Aunts coffee table, and I was instantly grabbed by the cover- the beautiful red door, and I wanted a holiday read. I finished it in just over a day, and really enjoyed reading it. Then I had to pick up this one. &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016_12_reads_storm.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;storm&#34; /&gt;
Winter Storms(Winter 3) by Elin Hilderbrand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to summarize these books individually, because they really form a cohesive story. There are ups, there are downs. It shows how a family loves, grieves, and continues to move through life. A great holiday series. &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016_12_reads_eligible.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;eligible&#34; /&gt;
Eligible: A Modern Retelling of Pride and Prejudice by Curtis Sittenfeld&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Book club book! Alright, so I moved in July- but I miss my book club! They keep me in loop with what they are reading, and I try to read them even if I&amp;rsquo;m not there for the fantastic conversation and great food/drinks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, I needed to read this. I WILL READ ANY FORM OF PRIDE AND PREJUDICE EVER. So, did I like this book? YES. I loved it. ITS P&amp;amp;P! In the beginning I was a little irritated by the &amp;ldquo;modern&amp;rdquo; aspect, but after a few chapters I fell into the new rhythm and I honestly like what they did with the characters. I&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping this one. &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars (bias)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016_12_reads_crooked.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;crooked&#34; /&gt;
Crooked Kingdom by Leigh Bardugo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kaz and his crew are BA. Seriously. It makes me want to climb over roofs and scheme! This book, like the first, will keep you on your toes. Not even you will know what Kaz is up to, until he wants you to know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without giving spoilers, I will say that this final book tied into the Grishaverse and I was SO pleasantly surprised by that! &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016_12_reads_cabin10.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cabin&#34; /&gt;
The Woman in Cabin 10 by Ruth Ware&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first few chapters, I was really concerned that this book would be too much like Girl on the Train (which was a great book, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to read the same story)..(unless its p&amp;amp;p). It wasn&amp;rsquo;t! A tale all of its own. I was surprised, I think the ending was brilliant, and I recommend! &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016_12_reads_attitw.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;time&#34; /&gt;
All the Time in the World by Caroline Angell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book was so heart breaking and uplifting at the same time. Not uplifting in a everything turns out perfect way, but in a life goes on way. I cannot imagine the burden of the loss these characters face, and yet, I feel like Angell did a wonderful job of showing us different aspects of being human and helped me relate to the characters. &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016_12_reads_ove.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ove&#34; /&gt;
A Man Called Ove by Fredrik Backman&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;READ THIS BOOK! So, three chapters into this book I loved Ove. 5 Chapters in I said it would be one of the best books I read in 2016. By the end, it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite books ever. Ove is reminiscent of Carl Fredricksen from the movie UP and has a bit of Gran Torino to it as well. One page, Ove will have you laughing, and the next he&amp;rsquo;ll have you in tears. I think that I learned something from Ove, and that we can always use a new prespective. &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, I read Paper Princess by Erin Watt; I don&amp;rsquo;t have a picture of this book, and I gave it zero stars on Goodreads. Why? Because I was so shocked by the book that I was not ready to process it. I&amp;rsquo;m still not, so I&amp;rsquo;ll hold off on that. Here is what I will say: The main character is a girl in high school. She meets a boy and it becomes more of an erotic genre than what I had expected- I expected a YA book! Now, I see people saying this is NA&amp;ndash; I DO NOT AGREE. NA should bridge the gap of teen and adult- but if I was doing Readers Advisory for New Adult, I would NOT include this as an option (and if you are, perhaps you should mention the main theme). Hey, as far as erotic novels go- it was okay. But NA? No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stars are based on what I gave the book on Goodreads. However, you should know that I am particularly stingy with my 5 stars. Also, I don&amp;rsquo;t read bad books. As in, I might start a book, and if I don&amp;rsquo;t like it, I put it down. Life is too short to read bad books.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Weekly recap: Holiday Travel &amp; 2017 Goals</title>
          <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_01/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 16:11:58 &#43;0530</pubDate>
          <author></author>
          <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_01/</guid>
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It has been a crazy week, but it was full of family, friends and ended with the start of the New Year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016chrismukka.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chrismukkah&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Christmas Eve we drove up to Rochester to see my Aunt and cousins. My Aunt throws a &amp;ldquo;Chrismukkah&amp;rdquo; party, and her best friend brings her two adorable girls, her husband, and their parents. It was great to see them all again- to practice my lazy ASL and get an insight to RSL (The grandparents speak RSL and know hardly any ASL!). It was a lot of fun, it&amp;rsquo;s always crazy to see how fast those kids grow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_snap.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chrismukkah&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christmas day we spent with Zac&amp;rsquo;s family (and OF COURSE, Cheered on the STEELRS!). It was a really great day, and it was such a wonderful time of year to catch up with everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were in town we got to visit some new local places- a brewery, a cider mill and a coffee place (which we ended up at more than once). Everything we had was awesome, and I hope these local businesses are really successful this year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_drinks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drinks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also stopped at Wegmans, so that I could get my fill of Wegmans-brand products. Call me crazy, but the White Shells Mac &amp;amp; Cheese is unlike any other brand. We actually got flagged going through airport security because I stuck 12 boxes in Zac&amp;rsquo;s carry on&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of getting home- thankfully Zac is a seasoned flier now! We arrived at the airport and it was completely closed down for suspicious activity. Zac called the nearest airport, and got us out from there. Luckily we had great family members driving us all around!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016airport.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;airport&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We made it home late Thursday, and were greeted Friday by a BEAUTIFUL Denver Winter day. It was 60 degrees! So, after picking up Rex, we took a walk to Avanti&amp;rsquo;s for lunch. We love it there. So much to choose from, and it all tastes so fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016denver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;denver&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To end the year, we ended up dog sitting for a dog friend. Leo was a sweet addition to the evening, and we spent some time cuddling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2016nye.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dogs&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that you had a great holiday season! HAPPY 2017!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01_rexny.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
      
    

  </channel>
</rss>
