<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/categories/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mihshhehl.github.io/categories/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Balance</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_18/</guid>
      <description>So this past week was my first at Galvanize, but there was time outside of class! I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to break up my posts between school work, and life outside of class..
This past week Zac was in Portland, so every night we caught up on my day! I think he was as excited as me that I started school.
Monday I came home and just relaxed. All week it was really great that I had easy meals ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A busy relaxing week</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_08/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been so gorgeous here lately, that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that a week ago everything was covered in ice! We had a nice day, and right as the sun was setting, starting getting some drizzle. Well, it all turned to ice and our walk that night and the next morning was treacherous.
I am officially in the last week of the January 2017 Tone It Up Challenge! I&amp;rsquo;m loving it, and I plan to keep it up afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>659 Square Feet</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_05/</guid>
      <description>Back in July we moved out of our house in NY. It was a 1,452 sqft house (not including the full finished basement, or the bonus room above the garage). We moved from a house with four bedrooms, and two bathrooms to a one bed, one bath apartment. A mere 659 sqft. Here, my friends, is how we make it work..
FULL DISCLOSURE: We also have a storage unit. It&amp;rsquo;s small, and contains our spare tires, tool box and bikes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>