<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/categories/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://libmb.github.io/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s that smell?</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_03_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_03_25/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;During undergrad I spent one year working as an RA. I had a double room all to myself. I cozied it up, and made it my own. One day, a resident stopped by.. “Your room smells so good. I just HAD to tell you. I can smell it all the way down the hall! I love it”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/dorm.png&#34; alt=&#34;my dorm room&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wait? Really? I was surprised. I mean, my room was clean and cute&amp;ndash; for a dorm. But smell? I had bought an oil diffuser set from Target, and I was totally nose blind to the smell. Sure enough, when I came back from a holiday break, my room smelled amazing! I bought 2 more diffusers that year (same smell, same brand). That first resident wouldn’t be the last one to compliment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/light.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lit candles&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I guess it made sense&amp;hellip; Since I was younger, I’ve had a love affair with candles. My mom use to attend candle parties. Beforehand, I always got a look at the catalog and picked out my favorites. Today: book theme candles, wine candles, great-smelling candles, ok-smelling candles, summer candles, winter candles, diy candles, farmers market candles, special wick candles, candle melts, &lt;strong&gt;OH MY GOSH SIGN ME UP.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;get-scenty&#34;&gt;GET SCENTY&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentially, for the sake of this post, I am a self declared smell connoisseur. Based on my experiences, here are my tips for a great whole house scent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;pick-a-scent&#34;&gt;PICK A SCENT.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, I think this one is the hardest. Not a specific scent like “French Countryside”. Pick a main scent family like floral, bakery, fresh, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/candlemaker.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Candle Maker Site&#34; /&gt;
- &lt;a href=&#34;https://thecandlemakersstore.com/fragrances/fragrance-categories.html&#34;&gt;From: The Candle Makers Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? For a couple years, I wanted every room to have it’s own scent. The laundry/bath rooms would be ‘fresh’, the kitchen would be bakery, the bedroom would be calming&amp;hellip; I ended up with OK smelling areas, and no cohesive feeling. By picking one scent and spreading it throughout you can create an actual feeling within your home- as well as a signature scent that belongs to your home alone. There is nothing better than someone thinking, “Oh, this smells like your house” -in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;start-with-your-base-smell&#34;&gt;Start with your base smell&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is going to be you main, favorite, scent. It should define your scent category. It’s going to guide the way you decide in the upcoming step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;add-scent&#34;&gt;Add Scent&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we&amp;rsquo;re not putting different smells all over, we definitely want to have some variety. You’ll want to compliment the base scent with a few others. Pick ones that are in the same scent category, and have similar undertones. The goal is to pick scents that are similar enough that they blend together, but varied enough that the end smell is unique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;change-up-your-delivery-methods&#34;&gt;Change up your delivery methods&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s important that you have a few options for infusing your home with your scent. Candles are wonderful, but emit the best smell while burning (I also suggest keeping the lid off the candle when not burning, you will get a slight scent this way). Some other options include diffusers, plug in diffusers, oils, warmers, potpourri, spray and cleaning supplies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;disperse&#34;&gt;Disperse&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the major components of a ‘house scent’ is that the smell seems to come from everywhere and not one place. The larger the house, the more effort will need to be made, the smaller- the easier. You’ll want more scent in larger spaces, and those that have high foot traffic, and less in smaller areas. But don’t count out closets and cupboards (&amp;amp; I always stick a cheap diffuser under my sink next to my garbage can).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;maintain&#34;&gt;Maintain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it! You have a house full of your favorite scent. Every month you should flip your reeds in your reed diffusers, and restock candles as needed. Also, take a break and get away once in awhile. When you come home, you’ll be amazed by how good it smells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;last-tip-if-you-want-to-change-up-smells-do-it-gradually-switch-out-a-diffuser-here-a-candle-there-until-you-ve-replaced-everything-this-way-your-old-scent-will-blend-into-your-new-one&#34;&gt;Last tip: If you want to change up smells, do it gradually. Switch out a diffuser here, a candle there, until you’ve replaced everything. This way your old scent will blend into your new one.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;our-scent&#34;&gt;OUR SCENT&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we moved out to Colorado I completely fell back in love with fir trees. It’s funny, because we had them in NY, and I always loved the smell, but moving here- I just ADORE them and their fantastic varied smell. We had been hiking a bunch, and I couldn’t get enough of them. I decided to bring that home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/rmnp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;RMNP&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;scent-category&#34;&gt;Scent Category:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crisp Warm (I knew I wanted FIR as the base, so I kind of skipped this step)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;base-scent&#34;&gt;Base Scent:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.thymes.com/Fragrances/Frasier-Fir/&#34;&gt;Thymes Frasier Fir&lt;/a&gt;:  “Crisp Siberian Fir needles, heartening cedarwood, relaxing sandalwood”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/Thymes.png&#34; alt=&#34;Thymes&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;varied-scents-yankee-candle&#34;&gt;Varied Scents (Yankee Candle):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mistletoe: “Woody scents of mistletoe, berries, pine boughs and holly”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balsam &amp;amp; Cedar: “Balsam, aromatic cedarwood and juniper berry blend”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christmas Wreath: “Fresh-cut boughs and branches of pine, balsam and hollyberry”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/living.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;living room&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/bath.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bathroom&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three varied scents tie into the main scent with fir/pine notes. The Balsam &amp;amp; Cedar go the next step and blend into cedarwood. Lastly, the other two varied scents tie into the balsam &amp;amp; cedar with berry scents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/bedroom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bedroom&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/desk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bathroom&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;disperse-1&#34;&gt;Disperse:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a small apartment right now, so I picked two methods- diffusers and candles. For our base scent, I purchased three Thymes Frasier Fir diffusers. A large one for the living/kitchen area, and two small ones for the bedroom and bathroom. Then, bouncing around the apartment I have two large jar mistletoe candles, one Frasier fir candle and three small candles (mistletoe, Christmas wreath and balsam &amp;amp; cedar).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/kitchen.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;kitchen&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;more-varied-scents-cleaning&#34;&gt;More Varied Scents (cleaning):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have the Frasier Fir all purpose cleaner, and I wipe down the counters once in awhile. In addition, we use the Williams-Sonoma Winter Forest soap and room spray. (The hand soap is expensive, so I mix it with a cheap light-scented soap)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/fraiserfir.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;frasier&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Williams-Sonoma - Winter Forest: &amp;ldquo;Invigorating collection mingles the clean scent of pine with cedar wood, cinnamon, patchouli, thyme and citrus&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/soap.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soap&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/spray.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spray&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love our scent. When we went away for the holidays this year and came back, it smelled so good. I might change it up in a couple months. Or, maybe, this one could be a keeper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By the way, if I only ever get candles as gifts from this post on in my life, that’s excellent.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>