<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>crafts on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/categories/crafts/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in crafts on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://libmb.github.io/categories/crafts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitness &amp; Friends</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Friday night we went out for Thai! As usual, Zac ordered the better dish. Mine was a little (way) too spicy for my likes, so I helped Z out a bit. It was good, but we&amp;rsquo;ll still be on the hunt for Denvers best Thai!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/thai.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday night we went out for a few drinks. We wanted to stay close, since Zac was still recovering. We headed to Zengo, but they had a huge Year of the Rooster celebration going on, and we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to get in the door! So we went next door to McLoughlins. It was probably for the better. They were playing great 90s music and had the X Games on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/drinks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drinks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Australian Open was on at 1 am, so we (Zac) were determined to stay up for it! Rafa and Fed? It was sure to be a great match, and from what I&amp;rsquo;ve heard, it was! I fell asleep as soon as it started. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t stay up another minute! Zac was a champ and watched the whole thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/aus.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tennis&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday Zac was super tired from his late night so we pretty much just hung out and watched The Man at the High Castle. I went to the gym, of course. The workouts are still great, and this week they&amp;rsquo;re amping them up a little. It&amp;rsquo;s great timing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/fitness.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made omelettes for breakfast with the veggies I had left over from the week. We also tried the Ginger Sesame Chicken from TIU and it was fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/food.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday I took Rex on some errands. During the weeks while Zac is gone I try to take Rex everywhere. It helps keep his energy down! Monday I rewarded him with a quick stop at Krisers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/errands.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Amazon order came in Monday afternoon. Two more of the BEST sports bras, and a new container of ACV. I spent the afternoon meal prepping. I made Almond Butter cookies for the cookie smoothie on the plan this week. Its delicious! I also made some Cinnamon Energy Bites to take to craft night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/drink.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drinks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before leaving for the evening, I took Rex for a nice long walk. We got some really good views of the sunset. I do wish I could grab a photo that does the mountains justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday I grabbed a lyft to Cojos for Craft Night! I missed the last few months due to holiday travel, and I&amp;rsquo;m so excited I finally made it. Ladies, wine, food, crafts. What else could you want in an evening? I even managed to organize someones prismacolor pencils. Because, personality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ALSO BTW. Lyft/Uber rides are my favorite thing since moving to Denver. Really. Someday I&amp;rsquo;ll give a little rave for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/craft.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;craft&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I cleaned up and took a bunch of photos for my next blog post. I also caught up on The Vampire Diaries. Zac&amp;rsquo;s sister, Mel, and I are the hugest TVD Fans. This week when NINA posted that she&amp;rsquo;d be coming back- we pretty much freaked out. I AM SO EXCITED.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/tvd.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tvd&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I have some precourse work to start for gSchool&amp;hellip;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>