<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mealprep on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/categories/mealprep/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mealprep on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mihshhehl.github.io/categories/mealprep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is close...</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_12/</guid>
      <description>Energy was pretty low this week, and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t feeling fantastic some days- but it was a good week.
Monday night we rented Dr. Strange. IT WAS SO GOOD. It&amp;rsquo;s actually probably one of my favorite movies now. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to own it and watch it again and again&amp;hellip; I HOPE there is another (&amp;amp;soon).
Tuesday was my early day so we hit the gym and took it easy.
Wednesday Zac and I grabbed lunch at Brider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another week goes by!</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_05/</guid>
      <description>SO MANY PHOTOS IN THIS POST&amp;hellip;
Last Sunday was a prepare for the week day! Steph and Geoff had just left on Saturday, so I spend Sunday catching up around the house, grabbing groceries, and mostly meal prepping!
We stopped at the container store, and Zac ensured that I contained myself. Still my fav.
Monday night was craft night! I headed over to Cojo&amp;rsquo;s with my banner supplies for Stephs Shower!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful weekend</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_12/</guid>
      <description>Last free weekend before Galvanize was wonderful! Thursday evening I headed over to Galvanize for an informal get together- saying HI before starting on Monday. I met Kiki, our class dog!
Thursday night we headed out to Avanti for dinner. It was a gorgeous night, and we stopped by Prost first.
It was so nice to sit outside and chat about life. Then we headed to Avanti, we sat downstairs, ordered some pizza for National pizza day, and went up to the roof for a little while.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>