<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gym, Happy Hour &amp; Life</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_04_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_04_02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am still feeling so incredibly spoiled for having Zac home. I know that he&amp;rsquo;ll be starting another project soon and be back to traveling, but I am loving having him home!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/zr.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;z and rex selfie&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday I finally did something I have been thinking about for a while. I deactivated Facebook. Seriously, I have wanted to get it out of my life for awhile. I was spending too much time doing nothing on there- and actually just hated it. I thought it was hilarious that once I decided to deactivate, it takes you through multiple options of PLEASE DON&amp;rsquo;T. But there was no turning back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/m.facebook.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Facebook&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday and Friday Rex went to Galvanize with me, which was great but also meant that I was trying to get some dog exercise in before hand every morning!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/r.galrex.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got in some really good gym sessions this week. I am still loving everything about Tone It Up and I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to the bikini series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/f.gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/f.gym2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/t.gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Friday I watched most of the mens tennis match on the elliptical. It was an INSANE match. I&amp;rsquo;m so glad Fed won!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/f.tennis.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday Zac and I went to the Galvanize/Pivotal gym to do some Rowing. It was active recovery day for me- So it was a good day to work in something we don&amp;rsquo;t usually get to do. We did a 5-4-3-2-1 partner row for a total of 3000! We made pretty good time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/s.row.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;row&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/s.row2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;row&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we played some ping pong. I need some practice to keep up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, we headed to Public School 303. They have a GREAT happy hour (&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; liter of wine). We grabbed a few apps and chatted for awhile. It is really cool that we can talk about tech in a new way now. Things I would not have understood, at all, just months ago we can now talk about at length.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/s.ps.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Public School&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/s.ps2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Public School&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Saturday night we made some popcorn and watched a movie. I love honey powder with popcorn SO MUCH. There is a local store down the road that sells a ton of spices, and this one is a winner. Saturday night, I was literally asleep by 9:30. &lt;strong&gt;win&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_02/s.popcorn.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Popcorn&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another week down.. and up next is another week with Zac home!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m2w1</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_04_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_04_01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I CAN&amp;rsquo;T BELIEVE ITS ALREADY QUARTER TWO. WHOOOP! Time is FLYING! The walk in on Monday morning felt pretty good. Ready to start again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/m.walk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Platte St&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday and Tuesday we were reviewing Q1 materials to prep for our Wednesday Assessment. Tuesday was early day again. Proof that I was totally off my game is that I accidentally brewed two pots of coffee in one pot. I came out and saw it overflowing onto the counter- &lt;strong&gt;ugh!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/t.coffee.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tuesday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/t.morning.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tuesday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday was assessment- and I loved it. We were given a wireframe and user stories and the whole day to deliver the product. It was a long day, but I enjoy the full projects that we work on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/w.assessment.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wednesday assessment&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/w.ass2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Stories&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday and Friday our apartment complex was doing fire alarm testing so Rex was a gSchool student!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/r.rex.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/r.rex2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/r.rex3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s actually really nice to bring Rex in, because during breaks I go outside with him. I feel like the fresh air does good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/r.outside.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/r.outside2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday we learned a couple new things- first we covered Node.js- I have to take some time this weekend to review that in more depth..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/r.node.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were also introduced to npm, and they did an AWFUL but very helpful exercise with evil npm packages. Pretty much- I know to review and research anything I ever download from npm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/r.npm.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;npm&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday gWomen held a lunch- it was nice to get together and chat. I look forward to meeting with the ladies more! I did think it was funny because a few of us had &amp;lsquo;packed&amp;rsquo; lunches which were really just like food items in their original packaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/r.lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was a scrimmage day. We did paired programming and I LOVED IT. My partner and I worked together really well, and avoided so many small mistakes by working together. We finished pretty early, and felt good about what we did!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac brought me some lunch- Protos Pizza! I love it so much, and was crazy grateful that he brought it for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/f.lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pizza lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/f.lunch2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pizza lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, I took Rex home. We got an email that alarm testing was done- and there was a large dog that was giving him some anxiety. We headed home in the rain, and on the way back I grabbed a latte at Ink for warmth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/f.rain.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rain&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_04/2017_04_01/f.latte.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;latte&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, it was a slower week for Galvanize. But I think we needed it, and I still learned a few important things. I think this quarter is going to be really hard, but I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be learning again!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITS BREAK WEEK</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_27/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At the end of project week, I was feeling pretty good (energy wise). I fully expected myself to be spending my break days coding and learning! As it turns out, I had no idea how badly I needed a break until I had it. I started a few projects here and there, and worked on a few things. But mostly, I did laundry and errands-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Monday, I started working on an Atom Package. Zac was a huge help- I don&amp;rsquo;t have much experience with classes yet, so there was a learning curve that he helped me through. It&amp;rsquo;s still a work in progress, but a really cool project to work on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/m.atom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Atom Package&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday Zac went to Wash Park to do some tennis drills. Rex and I went down and walked the park while he played.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/m.tennis.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wash Park Tennis&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday my new phone case came in! I ordered the same exact one I&amp;rsquo;ve had. After a few drops, my phone is still in perfect condition, but the case was compromsied. I feel better having a sturdy one again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/phonecase.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Android case&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday night I was TAing for an intro to JavaScript class and stopped by the fundamentals class to say Hi! James has been with that class since the start, and was helping out with a few homework problems before class. I think that Galvanize needs to tweak a few aspects of that class- it just is not working how it should- and from what I have seen, does not meet the Galvanize Standard that I am use to. Until then, starting next week I&amp;rsquo;ll be helping out regularly there too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/t.james.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;JS Fundamentals&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday night an old friend from HS was coming for dinner- so I spent the day cleaning up and grooming Rexy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/w.rexbath.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wet Rexy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mid day, I met Zac for lunch at Denver Beer Co. Food truck was stir fry! It was really good, and so nice outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/w.lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Lunch date &#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/w.lunch2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Lunch date &#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/w.lunch3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Lunch date &#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dinner was fun, and we found ourselves looking through year books - remembering random stuff and being super happy that we&amp;rsquo;re not still in high school (because awful).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/w.dinner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Yearbooks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday was another beautiful day. A friend who lives in the complex had taken the day off- so we sat up on the rooftop balcony and got some sun. Leo, her dog, is such a cuddler. He did not care that it was like 80 degrees in full sun- he was happy to curl up in my lap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/r.leo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Balcony&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/r.rex.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Balcony&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After, Rex and I got some work done outside. BECAUSE ALL THE SUN PLEASE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/r.outside.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Balcony&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday night I TAed for Free Code Camp and had a blast. I highly suggest it to Galvanize Students. Everyone was at different points in learning, but it was fun to engage and talk through various problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By Friday, I realized that my ideal week didn&amp;rsquo;t happen. I had been hitting the gym at 9pm instead of 6am, hadn&amp;rsquo;t finished any projects and definitely didn&amp;rsquo;t refactor anything from Q1. But- it was super successful and needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/gym2.png&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend we relaxed. Got lattes, made pancakes and generally took it easy before I head back for Q2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/s.latte.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saturday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/s.mask.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saturday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/s.pancake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saturday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fun fact is that I cannot make pancakes. Listen- I don&amp;rsquo;t know. I just don&amp;rsquo;t know what I do wrong EVERY time. So- after many failed attempts, Zac is the official pancake maker here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/s.pancake2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saturday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We rented Passengers Saturday night- it was SO GOOD. Way different than I expected- I love it when a trailer doesn&amp;rsquo;t tell you the full story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/s.passengers.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;saturday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday is run-day, and we did a family run! I think we all did really good. Running in Denver is rough. We finished our three miles and felt pretty accomplished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_27/u.runday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunday&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday afternoon we grabbed groceries, and did a little meal prep. THEN it was time for TWD! I can&amp;rsquo;t believe next week is the season finale&amp;hellip;. ANXIETY!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s that smell?</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_25/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;During undergrad I spent one year working as an RA. I had a double room all to myself. I cozied it up, and made it my own. One day, a resident stopped by.. “Your room smells so good. I just HAD to tell you. I can smell it all the way down the hall! I love it”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/dorm.png&#34; alt=&#34;my dorm room&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wait? Really? I was surprised. I mean, my room was clean and cute&amp;ndash; for a dorm. But smell? I had bought an oil diffuser set from Target, and I was totally nose blind to the smell. Sure enough, when I came back from a holiday break, my room smelled amazing! I bought 2 more diffusers that year (same smell, same brand). That first resident wouldn’t be the last one to compliment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/light.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lit candles&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I guess it made sense&amp;hellip; Since I was younger, I’ve had a love affair with candles. My mom use to attend candle parties. Beforehand, I always got a look at the catalog and picked out my favorites. Today: book theme candles, wine candles, great-smelling candles, ok-smelling candles, summer candles, winter candles, diy candles, farmers market candles, special wick candles, candle melts, &lt;strong&gt;OH MY GOSH SIGN ME UP.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;get-scenty&#34;&gt;GET SCENTY&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentially, for the sake of this post, I am a self declared smell connoisseur. Based on my experiences, here are my tips for a great whole house scent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;pick-a-scent&#34;&gt;PICK A SCENT.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, I think this one is the hardest. Not a specific scent like “French Countryside”. Pick a main scent family like floral, bakery, fresh, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/candlemaker.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Candle Maker Site&#34; /&gt;
- &lt;a href=&#34;https://thecandlemakersstore.com/fragrances/fragrance-categories.html&#34;&gt;From: The Candle Makers Store&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? For a couple years, I wanted every room to have it’s own scent. The laundry/bath rooms would be ‘fresh’, the kitchen would be bakery, the bedroom would be calming&amp;hellip; I ended up with OK smelling areas, and no cohesive feeling. By picking one scent and spreading it throughout you can create an actual feeling within your home- as well as a signature scent that belongs to your home alone. There is nothing better than someone thinking, “Oh, this smells like your house” -in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;start-with-your-base-smell&#34;&gt;Start with your base smell&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is going to be you main, favorite, scent. It should define your scent category. It’s going to guide the way you decide in the upcoming step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;add-scent&#34;&gt;Add Scent&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we&amp;rsquo;re not putting different smells all over, we definitely want to have some variety. You’ll want to compliment the base scent with a few others. Pick ones that are in the same scent category, and have similar undertones. The goal is to pick scents that are similar enough that they blend together, but varied enough that the end smell is unique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;change-up-your-delivery-methods&#34;&gt;Change up your delivery methods&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s important that you have a few options for infusing your home with your scent. Candles are wonderful, but emit the best smell while burning (I also suggest keeping the lid off the candle when not burning, you will get a slight scent this way). Some other options include diffusers, plug in diffusers, oils, warmers, potpourri, spray and cleaning supplies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;disperse&#34;&gt;Disperse&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the major components of a ‘house scent’ is that the smell seems to come from everywhere and not one place. The larger the house, the more effort will need to be made, the smaller- the easier. You’ll want more scent in larger spaces, and those that have high foot traffic, and less in smaller areas. But don’t count out closets and cupboards (&amp;amp; I always stick a cheap diffuser under my sink next to my garbage can).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;maintain&#34;&gt;Maintain&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it! You have a house full of your favorite scent. Every month you should flip your reeds in your reed diffusers, and restock candles as needed. Also, take a break and get away once in awhile. When you come home, you’ll be amazed by how good it smells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;last-tip-if-you-want-to-change-up-smells-do-it-gradually-switch-out-a-diffuser-here-a-candle-there-until-you-ve-replaced-everything-this-way-your-old-scent-will-blend-into-your-new-one&#34;&gt;Last tip: If you want to change up smells, do it gradually. Switch out a diffuser here, a candle there, until you’ve replaced everything. This way your old scent will blend into your new one.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;our-scent&#34;&gt;OUR SCENT&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we moved out to Colorado I completely fell back in love with fir trees. It’s funny, because we had them in NY, and I always loved the smell, but moving here- I just ADORE them and their fantastic varied smell. We had been hiking a bunch, and I couldn’t get enough of them. I decided to bring that home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/rmnp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;RMNP&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;scent-category&#34;&gt;Scent Category:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crisp Warm (I knew I wanted FIR as the base, so I kind of skipped this step)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;base-scent&#34;&gt;Base Scent:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.thymes.com/Fragrances/Frasier-Fir/&#34;&gt;Thymes Frasier Fir&lt;/a&gt;:  “Crisp Siberian Fir needles, heartening cedarwood, relaxing sandalwood”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/Thymes.png&#34; alt=&#34;Thymes&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;varied-scents-yankee-candle&#34;&gt;Varied Scents (Yankee Candle):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mistletoe: “Woody scents of mistletoe, berries, pine boughs and holly”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balsam &amp;amp; Cedar: “Balsam, aromatic cedarwood and juniper berry blend”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christmas Wreath: “Fresh-cut boughs and branches of pine, balsam and hollyberry”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/living.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;living room&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/bath.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bathroom&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three varied scents tie into the main scent with fir/pine notes. The Balsam &amp;amp; Cedar go the next step and blend into cedarwood. Lastly, the other two varied scents tie into the balsam &amp;amp; cedar with berry scents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/bedroom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bedroom&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/desk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bathroom&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;disperse-1&#34;&gt;Disperse:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a small apartment right now, so I picked two methods- diffusers and candles. For our base scent, I purchased three Thymes Frasier Fir diffusers. A large one for the living/kitchen area, and two small ones for the bedroom and bathroom. Then, bouncing around the apartment I have two large jar mistletoe candles, one Frasier fir candle and three small candles (mistletoe, Christmas wreath and balsam &amp;amp; cedar).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/kitchen.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;kitchen&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;more-varied-scents-cleaning&#34;&gt;More Varied Scents (cleaning):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have the Frasier Fir all purpose cleaner, and I wipe down the counters once in awhile. In addition, we use the Williams-Sonoma Winter Forest soap and room spray. (The hand soap is expensive, so I mix it with a cheap light-scented soap)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/fraiserfir.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;frasier&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Williams-Sonoma - Winter Forest: &amp;ldquo;Invigorating collection mingles the clean scent of pine with cedar wood, cinnamon, patchouli, thyme and citrus&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/soap.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soap&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/spray.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;spray&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love our scent. When we went away for the holidays this year and came back, it smelled so good. I might change it up in a couple months. Or, maybe, this one could be a keeper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By the way, if I only ever get candles as gifts from this post on in my life, that’s excellent.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_25/pinterest.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pinterest&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life this week..</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Time to recap the life portion of the school life balance from last week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday at the gym ALL OF THE DUMBBELLS WERE THERE. I have never seen this before. People suck at picking up after themselves&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/m.gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday night we grilled on the roof. We were hoping to catch some Tennis up there on the TV- but apparently our complex has different subscriptions in different rooms.. So after, we ended up back in the apartment subscribing to tennis channel&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/t.roof.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rooftop&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/t.roof2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rooftop&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week I have a cautionary tale for meal prepping&amp;hellip; I tend to use the same meals throughout the week. It makes shopping, prepping and cooking easier. But this week, I felt AWFUL after eating lunch on Monday. Due to food or not, I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t bring myself to eat the food I had prepped. Ugh- what a waste. I learned a lesson, and when I meal plan this week for Quarter two, I&amp;rsquo;ll be incorporating some variety through the week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So- food was basic- and I found a new combination I LOVE. My favorite Wegmans Granola and Coconut Noosa. Noosa is becoming my FAVORITE, slowly taking over my Chobani flip obsession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/m.lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;yogurt&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/m.yogurt.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;yogurt&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My new Micron pens came in this week! I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to start playing with them and some typography books. You know, when I have a second of free time again lol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/w.micron.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been so great to have Zac home. We&amp;rsquo;re getting totally spoiled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/w.dog.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;CAD&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday was REALLY exciting. First, my project in school was done- but after school we had a dinner and movie date!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We decided to go to a well known restaurant in downtown called Guard and Grace. It was wonderful. Everything was so good. I got a glass of red wine, a house salad and a 4 oz filet. If you want a steak in Denver, I highly recommend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/r.dinner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/r.dinner2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I totally bought tickets to Beauty and the Beast a month before it came out! IT WAS SO GOOD! AHHH! I CAN&amp;rsquo;T WAIT TO SEE IT AGAIN. I&amp;rsquo;ll be preordering that one&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/r.beauty.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Beauty and the Beast&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was the official start to break. I got home around 3:30- and sat in the sun, started my new Shades of Magic book and started relaxing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/f.book.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;book&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/f.dog.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cooked up on the roof again- enjoyed dinner in sun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/f.dinner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/f.roof.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rooftop&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 4 hours later I had Atom open starting a new project, because, who takes a real break?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning I made bacon and apple omelettes. I LOVE putting apples in with the bacon. Seriously, it&amp;rsquo;s a great combination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/s.breakfast.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;breakfast&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we went to Aurora for a bike sale. Didn&amp;rsquo;t find anything we needed, and so we headed to Cherry Creek so Zac could order his tux for the upcoming wedding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/s.cherry.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cherry Creek&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we got back, Zac went on a bike ride ( I NEED TO GET MY SHIT TOGETHER AND GO! - &lt;strong&gt;clip in pedal problems&lt;/strong&gt; ). I got some snaps from my cohort that there was a housewarming party about .5 miles away from where I live- so I popped over to say hi and meet some people. Hot Dudes Reading was on the table- FTW.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/s.house.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;HDR&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we decided to go for an easy hike. We have some goals this year- and should start training easy. We headed up to &lt;a href=&#34;http://dayhikesneardenver.com/glendale-farm-trail-douglas-county-open-space/&#34;&gt;Glendale&lt;/a&gt; to do a quick loop. After, we went into the off leash area and let Rex trot around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/u.glendale.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Hike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/u.off.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Hike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got home, I made Coffee Smoothies. I didn&amp;rsquo;t measure, but it was something like this:
- .5 Cup Almond Milk
- 1.5 Cup Coffee
- 2T Peanut Butter
- 2 Scoops Vanilla Protein
- 1T coffee grounds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were really good. Will be making more in the future, and playing with the ingredients!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/u.coffee.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;smoothie&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We grilled dinner, again, of course, &amp;lsquo;TIS THE SEASON!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/u.grill.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;grill&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Book Update is that A Conjuring of Light is AMAZING. All the feels, already. LOVE THIS WORLD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_21/u.book.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Book&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w5</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow, what a week! It seriously FLEW by. First, I&amp;rsquo;ll review some pictures from the week, then get into the nitty gritty of projects&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the weekend, I decided that Monday was the best day to bring Rex into class. It works for our schedule, and fits better with the general flow at school. He only stayed a half day- because, projects. Also, HE SHAMED THE FAMILY by deciding to mark a classmates bag. UGH REX WTH, MAN! The guy was super generous and I still feel awful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/m.rex.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;rexy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday morning we had a guest speaker- Dish Network! I only went because I was assured that I could sit in the back and do work - that it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be rude. I guess this is a good time to say that I did NOTHING special or extra this week. I didn&amp;rsquo;t attend any meet ups or go to breakout sessions. It was a busy week, and I prioritized what I thought was best for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/m.dish.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dish&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty much all week I worked upstairs, getting sun and fresh air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/t.upstairs.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Up&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/t.lion.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/w.balcony.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Balcony&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OK, BEFORE I jump into Friday, I&amp;rsquo;ll cover the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quarter one projects are the embodiment of what we&amp;rsquo;ve learned this quarter. I submitted two ideas last Friday, and was directed to a certain one. What did I work on all week? GX!: Gifting Experiences. I decided to make something that was important to me, and perhaps would make life a little easier. I am really passionate about gifting experiences rather than material items- and in the past few years have gained some insight and experience in doing so. My idea was to create a web app that would allow a user to sort through gifts and return ones that fit with their scenario.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The requirements included: valid HTML, CSS, JavaScript and CSS Framework. Connect to at least one external API, and deploy to a production environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/f.timeline.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;timeline&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, it took me all week. I used two API&amp;rsquo;s (for weather and location) and by Wednesday night, I had a MVP (minimal viable product). Thursday I cleaned it up- and Friday, presented! Being honest, it could use some work and in the future, I&amp;rsquo;d like to do things differently (for instance, NOT use a CSS framework- but design the site myself).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/api.png&#34; alt=&#34;Screen Shot&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top things I learned?: 1. Local storage! Whoop. 2. When generating ideas- consider how much of the outcome relies on your creating content. The main product of the web app I created was written rather than pulled. I could spend hours and hours updating that content to make it better; and the product is that content! In the future, I will highly consider that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/f.wireframe.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;wireframe&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was presentation day. We submitted our projects (Github, deployed and wireframes)- and spent about 2-3 minutes demo-ing our product. I was BLOWN AWAY by my awesome cohort. Like, way to go guys. After, we were released for lunch and to create a YouTube video tutorial. About an hour before we were due back for retro- we were all finished and a bunch of us sat outside at DBC across the street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/f.DBC.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;DBC&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we did Retro.. and PROJECT WEEK WAS COMPLETE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_18/f.retro.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;RETRO&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That means that I AM ON BREAK. One week. I &lt;strong&gt;plan&lt;/strong&gt; on getting a lot done- we&amp;rsquo;ll see!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, you can check out my deployed web app here:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://giftx-d0791.firebaseapp.com/index.html&#34;&gt;GX: Gifting Experiences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is close...</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Energy was pretty low this week, and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t feeling fantastic some days- but it was a good week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday night we rented Dr. Strange. IT WAS SO GOOD. It&amp;rsquo;s actually probably one of my favorite movies now. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to own it and watch it again and again&amp;hellip; I HOPE there is another (&amp;amp;soon).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/m.strange.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dr. Strange&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday was my &lt;strong&gt;early day&lt;/strong&gt; so we hit the gym and took it easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/t.gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday Zac and I grabbed lunch at Brider. It was delicious, and wonderful outside. Before leaving, we grabbed lattes to take back to work with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/w.lunchz.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/w.lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/w.lunchc.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday night we grilled some dinner and sat by the fire for a bit. It&amp;rsquo;s so nice to be outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/r.fire.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fire&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/r.fire2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fire&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday we had a long standing plan to meet up with some friends at Blake Street Vault. I was excited for Zac to try the fried cheese and HE DOESNT EVEN LIKE IT. I think he&amp;rsquo;s insane, and its by far the best. I guess more for me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/w.vault.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Blake street&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/w.ck.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Blake street&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday we rented another movie- Arrival. It was REALLY good. Much better than I expected&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/f.movie.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Movie rental&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, I did some meal prep- and that pretty much covered out week. Lot&amp;rsquo;s of relaxing and catching up on things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_12/s.mealprep.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sunday meal prep&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w4</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/m.donut.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Two boxes of Donuts!&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday morning two classmates pulled together to bring in a BUNCH of doughnuts! They are for sure not on the plan- but I had one and it literally made me happy- so there&amp;rsquo;s that. (ps. they were awesome for doing that).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/m.guest.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Guest Speaker&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started off the week with a guest speaker- a UX designer! It was a really interesting talk- and I appreciate seeing and hearing from different people in the tech field- who work in the various aspects of web development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/model.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;model map&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Topic wise- we covered models and deployed to Firebase. It was a gentle way to start the week! (And I think Kiki is warming up to me!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/m.molly.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mollys desk&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/m.kiki.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Kiki laying&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Tuesdays, I get in early to do some side work with a classmate- we kind of review the things we&amp;rsquo;ve gone over and talk about anything we&amp;rsquo;re stuck on. I was first in the basement, so I made all the fresh coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/t.coffee.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Coffee Pots&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also decided to take over our white boards. They were getting pretty messy and hard to read- so I decided to clean them up a bit and bring a little inspiration to the walls!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/t.board.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;White boards&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/t.stars.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;White Board image&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I go in early, I have a really hard time eating breakfast before hand. I pretty much just suck at getting up in the morning. Luckily- I know myself and meal prep! SO I brought breakfast and enjoyed it in the classroom. (Overnight oats for the win).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/t.break.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Breakfast&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Topic wise, we covered wireframes and closures&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/t.wireframe.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;wireframing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was feeling AWFUL on Tuesday. I actually contemplated leaving the entire day,  but my pain subsided after lunch and I pulled it off. Since I was feeling crappy- and wear my emotions on my sleeve- Jordan gave me his origami for the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/t.origami.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Origami&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He makes these everyday! Out of bus passes and random papers. They are AMAZING. I love them and wish I could make these things without looking them up..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday Izabella brought Ziggy to class! He was super sweet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/w.ziggy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was INTERNATIONAL WOMENS DAY and during stand up George gave a really, really nice little speech about it. (And I was really glad that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t the first to mention it during interestings!) Anyway, there were a lot of events going on that night- but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t make any of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/w.iwd.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IWD Event&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I finally completed a KATA submission on Wednesday, but it won&amp;rsquo;t load. I&amp;rsquo;m guessing that I&amp;rsquo;m missing something-  but i&amp;rsquo;ll have to come back to that later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/w.codewar.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Codewars&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday was BEAUTIFUL. I spent my free time outside. For lunch, Zac met me a Briders. They have a baby kale and apple salad he&amp;rsquo;s been raving about- so I had to try it so that we can make it at home! (it was actually fantastic).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/r.lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Zac at Lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During lecture, we discussed agile workflows and user stories. I was super excited to move into this discussion - because it&amp;rsquo;s such an important aspect of work at Pivotal and I had heard so much about it. Plus, we got to use Pivotal Tracker for logging user stories- it was a cool intersection of Zac&amp;rsquo;s life and my schooling!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/r.agile.png&#34; alt=&#34;Agile&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All afternoon, we working on assessments and brainstormed projects on the balcony. As mentioned, it was BEAUTIFUL!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/r.group.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Outside&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was PROPOSAL DAY. Oh gosh- FOUR WEEKS DONE? When did that happen&amp;hellip;. Week five is all about our personal project- so on Friday we wrote up proposals- submitting them for review and made revisions as needed. Mine ended up getting approved a couple hours before the end of the day- but I&amp;rsquo;ll save that for next week. What was REALLY exciting about Friday was that IT WAS REXY&amp;rsquo;S FIRST DAY AT GALVANIZE. Here he is being good boy at stand up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/f.rexstand.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a guest speaker- and he was pretty vocal during that (opps). He just wanted some water&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/f.rexspeaker.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex during speaker&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, we ironically did a agile exercise and it included a lot of tennis balls. Rex was super good though. And the exercise was awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/f.tennis.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tennis&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He pretty much just slept (because let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, I took him for a run before we went in).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/f.rexsleep.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sleeping rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We met Zac for lunch, and Rex went home with him after that- so that I could focus on some work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/f.lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex hotdog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So- that was week Four. A relatively easy going week to lead into projects. A great step with Rex. Lots of sun and fun. Here&amp;rsquo;s our updated Q1 learn map!:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_11/f.learn.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Whiteboard map&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack the Planet</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_06/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HACK THE PLANET WAS SO MUCH FUN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/hacktheplanet.png&#34; alt=&#34;Logo for Hack the Planet&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/me.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Selfie&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So Saturday I participated in my FIRST EVER HACKATHON. It was also the first ever gSchool hackathon. The event started around 8:30, but I showed up early to get put into a team. Since I&amp;rsquo;m still new to this world, and the event wanted to encourage cross cohort/location collaboration- I decided to go in as a single and get paired up with a group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/team.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Group Pic&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it worked out really great! Look at this crew. Molly is in g46 with me, two teammates are in g41 (about a month ahead of us), and one team member is a data science student. We were pretty well rounded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/molly.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Molly and I&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After everyone was grouped up- we got the rules from Josh! Goal was to use a NASA API and make a web app&amp;ndash; they amended this later to be any API (because reasons I don&amp;rsquo;t know..?).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/rules.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Josh giving rules&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 9:30 we got started. We brainstormed a bunch of ideas until one clicked. Molly had taken a meteorology class in undergrad, and her teacher watched the forecast for hail. He would collect it and make margaritas- according to him they make the best because they have ozone in them. Our idea- Hail Ya! was born.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The concept was to pull weather data- and plan a margarita party around forecasted hail!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First hiccup was that there was no hail forecasted in the US for, like, ever. Winter? SO we switched gears-  a web app that would pull 1. your location and 2. the weather forecast. We would pull the precipitation type and tell you what kind of drink to make based on what &amp;ldquo;natural&amp;rdquo; ingredients you could use!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/diagram.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;whiteboard planning&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We split off- and I started working on design. With the time crunch, I decided to go with &lt;em&gt;what I knew&lt;/em&gt; and so you can see- it mirrors what I created for this blog!:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/hailcomp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;picture of computer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I created 4 recipes based on the results for rain, snow, sun and the ultimate goal: hail!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 1:30 (pizza was delivered at noon), I wrapped up the design pieces and started collaborating on the CSS/HTML pages. At 3pm, we had finished our forms and layout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/screenform.png&#34; alt=&#34;Finished form&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/screenresult.png&#34; alt=&#34;Finished result page&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it was crunch time. Submission was due at 4:30 and we were struggling to get the last functions working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/struggle.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;struggles&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With minutes left we finished, and with seconds left we cleaned up our merge files and pushed our product to Github!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it was time to present- we were up first, which was actually awesome. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a picture of us, but I do have one of the team that won (they did AWESOME):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_06/present.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Winning team presentation&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seriously everyone did awesome. It was great to sit back and see what everyone had created- what they came up with and how they executed it! There wasn&amp;rsquo;t a single bad project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We didn&amp;rsquo;t win, but I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have changed anything. I had a great time with my team. I take away this: TIME FLIES SO FAST. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe we were there, seriously working, for 8 hours. But I also can&amp;rsquo;t believe what we were able to accomplish either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m excited for the next round- and to find a Hackathon I can enter with Zac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To end, I slept over 10 hours Saturday night.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another week goes by!</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SO MANY PHOTOS IN THIS POST&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/dognight.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Insert Random Dog Pic here&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last Sunday was a prepare for the week day! Steph and Geoff had just left on Saturday, so I spend Sunday catching up around the house, grabbing groceries, and mostly meal prepping!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/lastbreak1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;breakfast&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/lastbreak2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;breakfast&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/lastlunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We stopped at the container store, and Zac ensured that I &lt;em&gt;contained myself&lt;/em&gt;. Still my fav.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/csstore.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Container Store&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday night was craft night! I headed over to Cojo&amp;rsquo;s with my banner supplies for Stephs Shower!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/craftnight.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;banner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday night Zac and I did some work while on the couch. I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t watch a SINGLE SUPERNATURAL since gSchool started. WHICH IS CRAZY. How will I ever catch up at this rate? So I put that on..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/supercomp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;breakfast&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday night Zac went to a Learn to Code Colorado meetup with me. I&amp;rsquo;ll be TA-ing a class this month, and wanted to get some hands on experience. It was also great because Zac got to meet some of my instructors and peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/ltcc.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;LTCC&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac snagged a picture of me in my natural element (because helping)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/ltcc2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;LTCC&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday after class/work we went to the gym at the Galvanize/Pivotal building. After getting my moves in, Zac and I did a row OFF! It was fun, but mostly it was hard, lol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/gym2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/gym3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/row.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next thing we knew it was FRIDAY! I wore my new CF shirt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/cfshirt.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cloud Foundry&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mel and Cody planned a layover in Denver on their way to Mexico for their honeymoon! Zac met them at the airport at 6; and at 7 we headed to Avanti for dinner!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/mel.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mel &amp;amp; Cody&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/melcod.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mel &amp;amp; Cody&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/allfour.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mel &amp;amp; Cody&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it was time to head back to the airport! We grabbed icecream from Milkbox at union first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/icecream.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mel &amp;amp; Cody&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had the MOST AMAZING flavor. Seriously. Try it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/straw.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mel &amp;amp; Cody&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/mctrain.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mel &amp;amp; Cody&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the shortest visit, but it was good to see them and hug them! I hope they have a great vacation in sunny Mexico!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of SUN, our weather has been kind of crazy this week. But it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been awful, and we had some SPECTACULAR days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Insert Random Dog Pic here&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/sunsnow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Insert Random Dog Pic here&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday- I hack-a-thon-ed. Read that post for details!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we met up with Joe and his family for a quick dinner and some Ciders. They have seriously cute kids, and I had fun playing with them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/joe.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Joes baby&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I slept, like a lot. On Sunday I WAS DEAD TIRED (even after a full nights sleep). So, we woke up late, went to the gym, and after a long day, ran errands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stopped by the library and returned my books. I also cancelled all my holds. I haven&amp;rsquo;t read a single page in three weeks.  A SINGLE PAGE. Oh well.. in 5 months I&amp;rsquo;ll be back at it, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/bookbreakup.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;library returns&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got home, I meal prepped while listening to the new Ed Sheeran Album on Spotify. It&amp;rsquo;s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/thisbreak.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Meal Prep&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/thisbreak2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Meal Prep&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/thisdinner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Meal Prep&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I seriously can&amp;rsquo;t explain how much simpler meal prepping makes the week. It&amp;rsquo;s an investment on Sunday, but there is NO way I could eat healthy like this during the week otherwise. Here is a day(insert smoothie):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/allmeal.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Meal Prep&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life is PRETTY CRAZY around here, but I am loving every bit of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_05/dog.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Insert Random Dog Pic here&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w3</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_03_04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Week three of module one is officially complete! At the end of the week, I am feeling pretty great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/kiki.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;kiki&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday we covered objects, arrays and intro to jQuery. I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t looked at objects in months.. and for sure needed a refresher. I liked learning jQuery&amp;mdash; although I know to be careful in using it for all things in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week we had Roberto as our floating instructor. We got to hang with his AWESOME dog Iago-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/iago.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Iago the Dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday we covered HTTP and AJAX. AJAX is super helpful. Wednesday we moved on to CSS Frameworks (and had us all like, wth css!) and promises (which had us like, wth is this?). Covering CSS frameworks was so great- like a really neat shortcut to move faster when needed. Following that up with Promises left me feeling like it went right over my head. Luckily, the instructor came back on Friday and led a break out on promises to clarify and dig a bit deeper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/http.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;HTTP Whiteboard&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday we discussed higher order functions and the accumulator pattern. I loved these exercises. I pretty much use AP for all of the kata&amp;rsquo;s I try to solve on Code Wars, so I felt pretty equipped to tackle the assessment. Between HoF and AP, we had a ton of npm tests to pass. It was super satisfying to see those green checkmarks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/AP.png&#34; alt=&#34;AP Screen Shot&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/HOF.png&#34; alt=&#34;HoF Screen Shot&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was once again, scrimmage day! We started off with a guest speaker, and then we did a mini hackathon with a partner. We were trying to prep for the event on Saturday which most of the class signed up for. My partner and I used two API&amp;rsquo;s (punk beer and reddit) to make a random night generator. We managed to get it all functioning and throw up a materialize layout before time was up and we had to present. Afterwards, I was pretty amazed by what we could accomplish in a few hours- and was ready to participate in the Hack the Planet hackathon on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/randomnight.png&#34; alt=&#34;Scrimmage Screen Shot&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day Friday, we had another speaker. A Galvanize Instructor who had their last day and wanted to share their experience as a student &amp;gt; resident &amp;gt; instructor &amp;gt; software developer. All three webdev cohorts got together for it, and had a huge Friday stand down which Kyle led.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/standdown.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Group Stand Down&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After class on Friday, our resident organized a mentor/mentee happy hour (during First Friday Taco &amp;amp; Tequila hour) so we all went up to the fourth floor to meet some past students, current students and to of course enjoy some tacos!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/tacos.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tacos&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_03/2017_03_04/tequila.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tequila&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over all it was a really busy week- but I feel like we are learning so much. I&amp;rsquo;m going to need to set aside time during break week to review all of the things- but I am still just super happy to be learning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VISITORS</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning we cleaned up around the house- then headed to the airport to meet Steph &amp;amp; Geoff!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/airport.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sign&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, Steph brought supplies to restock our Wegmans necessities! &lt;em&gt;the best!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/wegmans.png&#34; alt=&#34;Food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were so excited to have guests, and there were so many places we wanted to take them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday evening we headed over to Galvanize, so I could show all three around my new school. We met an instructor and one of my cohort peers who was getting some work in. Zac and Geoff also squeezed in a game of ping pong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gschool.png&#34; alt=&#34;Galvanize&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we headed over to McLoughlins for a drink before going to Zengo for dinner with Zac and Stephs cousin, Danielle and her boyfriend Tim. After, we were still a little hungry, so we walked up to Littleman for some ice cream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/littleman.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;little man&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday we went to Eldora for a day of skiing/snowboarding. It was a pretty nice day, we were actually really warm but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to trek back to the car to ditch our jackets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/eldora.png&#34; alt=&#34;skiing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday night we headed out. First we stopped at Avanti for drinks and food. Then we went all the way to Larimer where we got a drink and took in the gorgeous view that is Larimer at nighttime. On the way home, we stopped by Rocket Fizz because its fun to browse candies that were around during our childhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/avanti_lar.png&#34; alt=&#34;avanti and larimer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday we went to the Botanic Gardens. It was SCFD Free day! It was free, and I am obsessed with the Gardens so it was a no brainer. Unfortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s winter, and so everything is dead. It was a little lackluster but the rainforest was still pretty awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gardens.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;botanic gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next we drove out to Boulder to do some walking along Pearl St. It was cold in the wind, but the sun was nice. We stopped for food and had the worst service.. but overall it was a nice day out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday night we headed to the hockey game!!!! And when we got there, it was empty! Ha, Zac had purchased tickets for a Tuesday game, thinking it was Monday. Instead we just walked over to PublicSchool303 for drinks and dinner. An old friend was in town, so she stopped by too and it was nice to catch up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/nothockey.png&#34; alt=&#34;not hockey&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday while I was in class, everyone went up to Red Rocks to explore. After class, I met everyone at Denver Beer Co, and we headed to the ACTUAL hockey game! The Avalanche are literally the worst team in the NHL, but sports are fun so it was worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/hockey.png&#34; alt=&#34;hockey&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday morning Steph joined me at the gym!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym buddy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday night Zac had gotten Steph and Geoff a hotel in Cherry Creek so they could have a night of vacation together! We went grocery shopping and did laundry&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday while I was in class, the group went to a brewery and an arcade. After, we went to Bones for dinner. It was a great meal, and the restaurant is nice and intimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/bones.png&#34; alt=&#34;bones dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was our LAST DAY. While I was in class Zac, Steph and Geoff headed to Keystone for some AWESOME skiing/snowboarding and I&amp;rsquo;m jealous! I would have loved to go, but i&amp;rsquo;ll get to next time. When I got home from school everyone was really tired and apparently the altitude was putting some stress on them. Zac stayed home while the three of us went down the road to My Brothers Bar for some dinner. It was ok.. but we were really hungry so it worked!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning, before leaving, we went and grabbed brunch at Carbon. We will miss them so much, but it was a GREAT week and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see them again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/carbon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;carbon brunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/bye.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge pic&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w2</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A short week! Monday we were off for Presidents day! Tuesday we started off covering test based assessments. Right now, we are using them for some of our assessments- but I look forward to Q2 when we learn how to write them! Now we have an updated flow/map of Q1:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/flow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;flow chart&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also spent some more time on Responsive CSS. I will say that by the end of this week, I feel much better about the topic and like flex box a lot more. I also really respect mobile first design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/css.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;css&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early this week I realized that I had some fierce competition on CodeWars. Its healthy, but is making me try harder katas and i&amp;rsquo;m trying to fit more in. One morning I worked on one for like three hours, and when I went to submit it I got a server error. No worries, I had it copied. It was funny.. (and I&amp;rsquo;m still losing)..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/codewars.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;codewars&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday we started JavaScript. I was super excited to switch it up and start another aspect of web dev. We covered the basics and did some assessments. During free time I headed upstairs to work from the &amp;lsquo;club galvanize&amp;rsquo; area. Stevie was in the classroom outside and I just love him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/stevie.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday after class, Galvanize had a guest speaker, the CTO at Rachio. I stayed to hear from him- about his company and the work they do (although, I have a friend who works there so I was already pretty familiar). It was really cool to see how involved their system is! If I had a yard I&amp;rsquo;d totally look into their product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday we learned DOM. I was not feeling well and it was really hard for me to process anything we learned. I took some medicine while on lunch and felt much better in the afternoon. I feel like I am getting better- but I still need to do some work to understand the basic concepts. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably dedicate some time to that this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/domfiddle.png&#34; alt=&#34;js fiddle screenshot&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On my way to class Friday I stopped for a latte. Because friday. and latte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/ink.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ink coffee&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday morning we had another guest speaker. This time it was Michael Dusing, a local UX Designer. He had a GREAT presentation about work, life and paths to success. I loved hearing from him, his slideshow was FANTASTIC and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to hear from more design people. He also brought stickers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/guest.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Guest Speaker&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we started another scrimmage day, while one-on-ones were going on. This week we worked on a pixel art creator. I got stuck a few places, and loved working with my table. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy with what I accomplished in one day- but have some stretch goals I want to work in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/pixel.png&#34; alt=&#34;Pixel Art&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_24/pixel2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Pixel Art&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Balance</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So this past week was my first at Galvanize, but there was time outside of class! I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to break up my posts between school work, and life outside of class..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This past week Zac was in Portland, so every night we caught up on my day! I think he was as excited as me that I started school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday I came home and just relaxed. All week it was really great that I had easy meals ready to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/mondinner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday was Valentines day! Rex got a treat of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/rexvday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Valentines&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Galvanize, I headed to the gym. A very nice lady decided to talk to me while I was on the elliptical. She was concerned that I was at the gym alone (also the only person in the gym) on Valentines. I explained that Zac was in Portland- but come on- who does that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/vdaygym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After going to the gym and talking to Zac, Rex and I watched some Twilight while working on some CLI Murder Mystery! It was a really fun way to practice command line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/vdayfun.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;CLI&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday my new bag came! I ordered an everyday tote- it is awesome! It has all of these collapsable dividers and is the perfect size. I love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/bag.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Peak Design Everyday Tote&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the CodePen Meetup, I headed to the gym at Galvanize. It was totally empty, and it was nice to change up the scenery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/ggym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday night Zac got home from Portland (and will be home for three weeks at least!!). I immediately had him run through a Git/Github exercise to explain some concepts for me. He&amp;rsquo;s a sweet guy..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/zacgit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;git hub&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All week I stopped home for Rex at lunch. All week he would watch me eat before heading to the dog park. He pretty much moped- I think he misses all our fun weekday adventures- but we&amp;rsquo;ll make it up on the weekends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/lunchrex.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rexy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The meal planning/prepping was lifesaving. It was the only reason I had time this week! AND, this week I had grapefruit as M2. I realized it has been 10 years since I had a grapefruit, and I LOVE THEM. So, I need to eat those more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;prepped lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/grapefruit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Grapefruit&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a really great week. The weather was nice, and it felt good to be busy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/weather.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;weather&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w1</title>
      <link>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mihshhehl.github.io/post/2017_02_17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WEEK ONE GALVANIZE!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/firstdayofschoolpic.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Picture First Day&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On day one, we played the name game &lt;em&gt;Mighty Michelle&lt;/em&gt; and met instructors, administrators, etc! Our first lesson was on &amp;lsquo;How to learn.&amp;rsquo; They served us a great lunch- wraps from protein bar!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Protein Bar&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My legs were super sore from runday on Sunday, and standing through the name game killed me! So, I sat on the ground. Nothing like a first impression-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/soreleg.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ground sitting&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, we got another tour, received our key fobs and talked about the Galvanize Culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/dayone.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;White board&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got to meet so many dogs! Kiki, as previously mentioned, is our class dog. Well- she is our residents dog so she&amp;rsquo;ll be hanging with us most days. The other two dogs belong to other instructors. Gosh I love being surrounded by them all the time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/dogs.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dogs&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After class on Monday, Galvanize organized a happy hour on the fourth floor to welcome us in. Everyone was invited (students, instructors, members).. and it was a pretty busy event! It was nice to meet some other people in the building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/happyhour.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Happy Hour&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday our first lesson was on POLYA- or how to solve problems. The day started with a warm up logic puzzle. My group didn&amp;rsquo;t do so great- apparently it relied on a lot of math and that is not my strong suit! Things to work on&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next we learned some command line and VIM. We had three assessments to work on- and things were officially getting started!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/polya.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Logic&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday we started with another logic puzzle. This time my group nailed it. I still need to practice though. I think i&amp;rsquo;ll grab a book next time i&amp;rsquo;m out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lessons on Wednesday were Git, Github and HTML. My table and I got into a serious discussion trying to figure out branching- hence our great use of the whiteboard table:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/branching.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Branch Pictures&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did the same when trying to conceptualize the process of setting remote vs. upstream with Git&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/upstream.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Upstream diagram&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday night there was a meetup at Galvanize for CodePen. I headed home to take care of Rex and grab some (PREPPED) dinner before going back. It was a really cool showcase of things people had made- how they made them, and why. At one point, a nine year old girl got up with her dad to show off her html/css project. I just about died- and I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I can apply to work for her in 6 months (exaggerating, but, not by much- she might rule the world someday).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/codepengroup.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Meetup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday we started responsive CSS. I pretty much got into fights with flex box all day. Luckily I wasn&amp;rsquo;t alone- and many of us found great tutorials and tools to help learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can we admire Kiki in her natural state? She is SO CUTE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/kiki.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sleeping kiki&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were also introduced to a concept called courage time. Pretty much we dedicate one hour to learning something we don&amp;rsquo;t know. We don&amp;rsquo;t need to have mastery in the topic- or even a fluency, but the point is that in one hour you can learn a lot- and accomplish a lot, in a topic you previously knew nothing about. I look forward to using courage time to delve into topics we might not cover in class (like design!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday- the final day of module one, week one! In the morning we had a guest speaker. She was a previous student who talked about her time, and what she is doing now! Then it was scrimmage day! Through the day, the instructors met with all the students for one-on-one meetings. While not in a meeting- we were working on our own site (using the skills we covered this week). I worked on a personal site. At 3, as usual, the keg was tapped- but they also had wine on tap! I grabbed a glass- and got my Galvanize swag! It was a great way to end the week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/wine.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;wine&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/swag.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;swag&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All week I packed my bag with Larabars as M4. It was the first time I tried them, and I absolutely LOVE cookie dough. The other flavors are really good too! They&amp;rsquo;ll probably become a regular thing for me..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mihshhehl.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_17/larabar.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Larabar&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>