<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hugo on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/categories/hugo/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in hugo on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://libmb.github.io/categories/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>VISITORS</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning we cleaned up around the house- then headed to the airport to meet Steph &amp;amp; Geoff!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/airport.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sign&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, Steph brought supplies to restock our Wegmans necessities! &lt;em&gt;the best!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/wegmans.png&#34; alt=&#34;Food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were so excited to have guests, and there were so many places we wanted to take them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday evening we headed over to Galvanize, so I could show all three around my new school. We met an instructor and one of my cohort peers who was getting some work in. Zac and Geoff also squeezed in a game of ping pong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gschool.png&#34; alt=&#34;Galvanize&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we headed over to McLoughlins for a drink before going to Zengo for dinner with Zac and Stephs cousin, Danielle and her boyfriend Tim. After, we were still a little hungry, so we walked up to Littleman for some ice cream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/littleman.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;little man&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday we went to Eldora for a day of skiing/snowboarding. It was a pretty nice day, we were actually really warm but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to trek back to the car to ditch our jackets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/eldora.png&#34; alt=&#34;skiing&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday night we headed out. First we stopped at Avanti for drinks and food. Then we went all the way to Larimer where we got a drink and took in the gorgeous view that is Larimer at nighttime. On the way home, we stopped by Rocket Fizz because its fun to browse candies that were around during our childhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/avanti_lar.png&#34; alt=&#34;avanti and larimer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday we went to the Botanic Gardens. It was SCFD Free day! It was free, and I am obsessed with the Gardens so it was a no brainer. Unfortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s winter, and so everything is dead. It was a little lackluster but the rainforest was still pretty awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gardens.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;botanic gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next we drove out to Boulder to do some walking along Pearl St. It was cold in the wind, but the sun was nice. We stopped for food and had the worst service.. but overall it was a nice day out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday night we headed to the hockey game!!!! And when we got there, it was empty! Ha, Zac had purchased tickets for a Tuesday game, thinking it was Monday. Instead we just walked over to PublicSchool303 for drinks and dinner. An old friend was in town, so she stopped by too and it was nice to catch up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/nothockey.png&#34; alt=&#34;not hockey&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday while I was in class, everyone went up to Red Rocks to explore. After class, I met everyone at Denver Beer Co, and we headed to the ACTUAL hockey game! The Avalanche are literally the worst team in the NHL, but sports are fun so it was worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/hockey.png&#34; alt=&#34;hockey&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday morning Steph joined me at the gym!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym buddy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday night Zac had gotten Steph and Geoff a hotel in Cherry Creek so they could have a night of vacation together! We went grocery shopping and did laundry&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday while I was in class, the group went to a brewery and an arcade. After, we went to Bones for dinner. It was a great meal, and the restaurant is nice and intimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/bones.png&#34; alt=&#34;bones dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday was our LAST DAY. While I was in class Zac, Steph and Geoff headed to Keystone for some AWESOME skiing/snowboarding and I&amp;rsquo;m jealous! I would have loved to go, but i&amp;rsquo;ll get to next time. When I got home from school everyone was really tired and apparently the altitude was putting some stress on them. Zac stayed home while the three of us went down the road to My Brothers Bar for some dinner. It was ok.. but we were really hungry so it worked!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday morning, before leaving, we went and grabbed brunch at Carbon. We will miss them so much, but it was a GREAT week and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see them again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/carbon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;carbon brunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_25/bye.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bridge pic&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Reads</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In December I finished 11 books. That&amp;rsquo;s CRAZY! I think that I associate the holiday season with curling up with a book.. and therefore take every opportunity to do so!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The books:
  The Graveyard Book Vol 1,&lt;br /&gt;
  The Graveyard Book Vol 2,&lt;br /&gt;
  Winter Stroll,
  Winter Storms,
  Eligible,
  Crooked Kingdom,
  The Woman in Cabin 10,
  All The Time in the World,
  A Man Called Ove,
  Paper Princess&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_GYB.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Graveyard&#34; /&gt;
The Graveyard Book by Neil Gaiman, and Craig P. Russell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Graveyard Book volumes were beautiful. I always wanted to get to this book- and when a friend tagged the graphic novel in her banned books post, it brought them up to the top of my list. I actually had hoped to read them in time for Halloween- but other library loans were ending and it got side tracked until December. I digresss.. This was a wonderful story- I love all the characters, and the different ways you can interpret the story itself. &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars | &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_Stroll.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;stroll&#34; /&gt;
Winter Stroll(Winter 2) by Elin Hilderbrand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked up the first book in this series, Winter Street, while I was visiting my family for Thanksgiving. The book was sitting on my Aunts coffee table, and I was instantly grabbed by the cover- the beautiful red door, and I wanted a holiday read. I finished it in just over a day, and really enjoyed reading it. Then I had to pick up this one. &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;4&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_storm.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;storm&#34; /&gt;
Winter Storms(Winter 3) by Elin Hilderbrand&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to summarize these books individually, because they really form a cohesive story. There are ups, there are downs. It shows how a family loves, grieves, and continues to move through life. A great holiday series. &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_eligible.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;eligible&#34; /&gt;
Eligible: A Modern Retelling of Pride and Prejudice by Curtis Sittenfeld&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Book club book! Alright, so I moved in July- but I miss my book club! They keep me in loop with what they are reading, and I try to read them even if I&amp;rsquo;m not there for the fantastic conversation and great food/drinks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, I needed to read this. I WILL READ ANY FORM OF PRIDE AND PREJUDICE EVER. So, did I like this book? YES. I loved it. ITS P&amp;amp;P! In the beginning I was a little irritated by the &amp;ldquo;modern&amp;rdquo; aspect, but after a few chapters I fell into the new rhythm and I honestly like what they did with the characters. I&amp;rsquo;ll be keeping this one. &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars (bias)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_crooked.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;crooked&#34; /&gt;
Crooked Kingdom by Leigh Bardugo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kaz and his crew are BA. Seriously. It makes me want to climb over roofs and scheme! This book, like the first, will keep you on your toes. Not even you will know what Kaz is up to, until he wants you to know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without giving spoilers, I will say that this final book tied into the Grishaverse and I was SO pleasantly surprised by that! &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_cabin10.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cabin&#34; /&gt;
The Woman in Cabin 10 by Ruth Ware&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first few chapters, I was really concerned that this book would be too much like Girl on the Train (which was a great book, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to read the same story)..(unless its p&amp;amp;p). It wasn&amp;rsquo;t! A tale all of its own. I was surprised, I think the ending was brilliant, and I recommend! &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_attitw.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;time&#34; /&gt;
All the Time in the World by Caroline Angell&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book was so heart breaking and uplifting at the same time. Not uplifting in a everything turns out perfect way, but in a life goes on way. I cannot imagine the burden of the loss these characters face, and yet, I feel like Angell did a wonderful job of showing us different aspects of being human and helped me relate to the characters. &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_05/reads_ove.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ove&#34; /&gt;
A Man Called Ove by Fredrik Backman&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;READ THIS BOOK! So, three chapters into this book I loved Ove. 5 Chapters in I said it would be one of the best books I read in 2016. By the end, it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite books ever. Ove is reminiscent of Carl Fredricksen from the movie UP and has a bit of Gran Torino to it as well. One page, Ove will have you laughing, and the next he&amp;rsquo;ll have you in tears. I think that I learned something from Ove, and that we can always use a new prespective. &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;5&lt;/sub&gt; stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, I read Paper Princess by Erin Watt; I don&amp;rsquo;t have a picture of this book, and I gave it zero stars on Goodreads. Why? Because I was so shocked by the book that I was not ready to process it. I&amp;rsquo;m still not, so I&amp;rsquo;ll hold off on that. Here is what I will say: The main character is a girl in high school. She meets a boy and it becomes more of an erotic genre than what I had expected- I expected a YA book! Now, I see people saying this is NA&amp;ndash; I DO NOT AGREE. NA should bridge the gap of teen and adult- but if I was doing Readers Advisory for New Adult, I would NOT include this as an option (and if you are, perhaps you should mention the main theme). Hey, as far as erotic novels go- it was okay. But NA? No.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stars are based on what I gave the book on Goodreads. However, you should know that I am particularly stingy with my 5 stars. Also, I don&amp;rsquo;t read bad books. As in, I might start a book, and if I don&amp;rsquo;t like it, I put it down. Life is too short to read bad books.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Travel</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It has been a crazy week, but it was full of family, friends and ended with the start of the New Year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/chrismukka.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chrismukkah&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Christmas Eve we drove up to Rochester to see my Aunt and cousins. My Aunt throws a &amp;ldquo;Chrismukkah&amp;rdquo; party, and her best friend brings her two adorable girls, her husband, and their parents. It was great to see them all again- to practice my lazy ASL and get an insight to RSL (The grandparents speak RSL and know hardly any ASL!). It was a lot of fun, it&amp;rsquo;s always crazy to see how fast those kids grow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/snap.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chrismukkah&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christmas day we spent with Zac&amp;rsquo;s family (and OF COURSE, Cheered on the STEELERS!). It was a really great day, and it was such a wonderful time of year to catch up with everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we were in town we got to visit some new local places- a brewery, a cider mill and a coffee place (which we ended up at more than once). Everything we had was awesome, and I hope these local businesses are really successful this year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/drinks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drinks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also stopped at Wegmans, so that I could get my fill of Wegmans-brand products. Call me crazy, but the White Shells Mac &amp;amp; Cheese is unlike any other brand. We actually got flagged going through airport security because I stuck 12 boxes in Zac&amp;rsquo;s carry on&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of getting home- thankfully Zac is a seasoned flier now! We arrived at the airport and it was completely closed down for suspicious activity. Zac called the nearest airport, and got us out from there. Luckily we had great family members driving us all around!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/airport.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;airport&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We made it home late Thursday, and were greeted Friday by a BEAUTIFUL Denver Winter day. It was 60 degrees! So, after picking up Rex, we took a walk to Avanti&amp;rsquo;s for lunch. We love it there. So much to choose from, and it all tastes so fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/denver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;denver&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To end the year, we ended up dog sitting for a dog friend. Leo was a sweet addition to the evening, and we spent some time cuddling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/nye.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dogs&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that you had a great holiday season! HAPPY 2017!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_01/rexey.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>