<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:19:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>64-ers, beautiful colorado &amp; ESPRESSO</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_21/</guid>
      <description>Monday was the first day of students in 64! It was SO GREAT meeting 25 new faces. It&amp;rsquo;ll take a few days to remember names, but the name game never fails to help.
This week I taught a couple lessons: Intro to CSS, Flexbox, Git/Github and some micro lessons on atom shortcuts and collaborating on Github. It was great, and stressful, but great. I&amp;rsquo;m learning so much- and really enjoying interacting with this new crew!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the week</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_25/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be a recap of the week- without anything from this coming weekend! It&amp;rsquo;s shorter, for sure. With less outside and sunshine. But TOMORROW- we move! I want to get all of the details from this past week out first.
First, the BIGGEST update, is that Zac surprised me with TWO PAIRS of ALL BIRDS. I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed! I got the light gray wool loungers and the heather gray runners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First week on the job!</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_13/</guid>
      <description>Monday was my first day as a Resident Instructor at Galvanize! It was a lot of meetings and getting access set up. I went to lunch with Brooks, the Lead Instructor for 64. We walked up to Uber Eats and I grabbed the highland salad. It was FANTASTIC.
Tuesday I was invited to lunch, and decided to go. I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to work on my ability to NOT go, but everyone was going and I figured it would be a good way to settle into the new role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break Week</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_08/</guid>
      <description>Last week was my week off before starting work! It feels just like a break week- and I used the time to recharge!
Friday was Graduation. It was adorable and short. The speeches were good, there was a lot of tears, and many hugs.
On Saturday I woke up and headed to Summer Soul! Kerry, a friend from undergrad, and Cojo came too. I love those yoga sessions so much. The ladies who run it are amazing, and I will go to as many as possible for ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready for an update?</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_08_03/</guid>
      <description>It has been a CRAZY THREE MONTHS. WHY, OH WHY haven&amp;rsquo;t I kept up with this?
Probably a mixture of things. First I was changing photo storage and that totally threw off my groove.
Then, school got intense, and I was saying yes to as many great amazing things as possible.
Something suffered, and it was this blog. But, I miss it. I wish I had kept up with it, and so- here we go again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT&#39;S BREAK WEEK</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_05_07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_05_07/</guid>
      <description>It feels so great to be on break week. School just builds and builds until project week, and by the end- it&amp;rsquo;s just exhausting. Having the week off is necessary.
Monday I spent some time outside. Rex and Leo went on an outing. In the afternoon, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t ready to let go of the sun yet- so I sat up on the roof for a little while.
Tuesday, I had a dentist appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It was snowy, it was sunny.</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_30/</guid>
      <description>There are week where you do a lot. And then there are weeks where you don&amp;rsquo;t. Then, there are weeks that are both. Ha- this was that! School was so busy with projects- that outside of school- it was necessary to take it easy!
Zac was gone again- so Rex and I went on lots of walks. Other than foundations- the only remarkable thing to happen during the week was that it was WEEK ONE OF THE BIKINI SERIES!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m2w5</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_29/</guid>
      <description>WOW. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about a fast week. A hectic, crazy, week! Group projects are great, and in some ways hard! That being said, WE MADE IT.
We started off our week by reviewing our pencil work. We established our project, our ERD, the wireframes and user stories. We combined all our ideas- and made sure that each of us had the same understanding of MVP and stretch goals.
From there- this whole week was this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hike &amp; Haircut</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_23/</guid>
      <description>This week Zac was in St. Louis again. Rex and I got in lots of exercise and a little relaxation. We got up a couple mornings and went for a run before the day. This keeps him tired when I&amp;rsquo;m away, or when I bring him in with me.
Monday night I rented Moana! It was adorable. I love Disney.
Tuesday night Rex came to Foundations with me. He was pretty good- and we had a really nice walk home afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m2w4</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_22/</guid>
      <description>This week we rolled through information! We had a lot to learn before projects next week- and we all had some sort of anxiety about either getting groups, or starting the project. This week we dived deeper into SQL joins, auth &amp;amp; auth, REST/CRUD, server side validation and FINALLY got our teams.
When we came in on Tuesday, we some new writing on our wall. A new goal is for all of us to add to the wall before graduation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Name.com HACKATHON!</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_19/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday night I went to my second hackathon! This one was hosted by name.com. The premise was we were given a domain name (cloud.denver) and two hours to make the best website for that domain. A lot of people showed up- and the place was packed! We ended up with a team that was wayy too big for a two hour hackathon- 10 people.
Our team name was DARE (given to us by the host).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigrants Make America Great</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_16/</guid>
      <description>As far as weeks go, this one was BUSY! Packed full of fun stuff.
Tuesday we signed up for a free bike class at REI. As for a free class, it was a good reminder. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since we&amp;rsquo;ve fixed a flat- and I think it as just what we needed there.
We also brought our dividend and grabbed a few things for hiking this year. We&amp;rsquo;re going to try and be responsible by stocking up on those &amp;lsquo;10 things every hiker should have&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m2w3</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_15/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t take my pictures this week at Galvanize. Must have been too busy learning or something&amp;mdash;-
We dived into even more topics this week! Including DATABASES, psql, ddl/ddm, and server side applications.
This week was all about the breakouts. Attending smaller size classes, for shorter periods, on concentrated topics. It had a few hitches, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t the worst.
Monday morning we had a guest speaker- Teagan. A BA developer at massroots- who has automated her entire home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m2w3</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_09/</guid>
      <description>I think that with school, and TAing JavaScript foundations every Tuesday and Thursday- the weeks are just flying by.
This week I had a lot of Greek Salads. Rather than making my own dressings from the TIU plan, I decided to just grab a bottle of healthy- clear ingredient- greek dressing. I had it practically every day- and it satisfied my craving!
On Thursday night, after TA, I spotted some 46ers at DBC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m2w2</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_08/</guid>
      <description>Week two of Mod 2 definitely picked up speed. After spending last week reviewing Q1, this week we dived into some new concepts- all gearing up for backend. We started: ES6, Express &amp;amp; Body parser.
Monday and Tuesday it was pretty cold. I really don&amp;rsquo;t mind being stuck in the basement when it&amp;rsquo;s snowy outside!
To start the week off on the right foot, I brought in CUPCAKES. Vanilla cupcakes with peanut buttercream frosting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gym, Happy Hour &amp; Life</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_02/</guid>
      <description>I am still feeling so incredibly spoiled for having Zac home. I know that he&amp;rsquo;ll be starting another project soon and be back to traveling, but I am loving having him home!
Monday I finally did something I have been thinking about for a while. I deactivated Facebook. Seriously, I have wanted to get it out of my life for awhile. I was spending too much time doing nothing on there- and actually just hated it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m2w1</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_04_01/</guid>
      <description>I CAN&amp;rsquo;T BELIEVE ITS ALREADY QUARTER TWO. WHOOOP! Time is FLYING! The walk in on Monday morning felt pretty good. Ready to start again!
Monday and Tuesday we were reviewing Q1 materials to prep for our Wednesday Assessment. Tuesday was early day again. Proof that I was totally off my game is that I accidentally brewed two pots of coffee in one pot. I came out and saw it overflowing onto the counter- ugh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITS BREAK WEEK</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_27/</guid>
      <description>At the end of project week, I was feeling pretty good (energy wise). I fully expected myself to be spending my break days coding and learning! As it turns out, I had no idea how badly I needed a break until I had it. I started a few projects here and there, and worked on a few things. But mostly, I did laundry and errands-
On Monday, I started working on an Atom Package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s that smell?K</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_25/</guid>
      <description>During undergrad I spent one year working as an RA. I had a double room all to myself. I cozied it up, and made it my own. One day, a resident stopped by.. “Your room smells so good. I just HAD to tell you. I can smell it all the way down the hall! I love it”
Wait? Really? I was surprised. I mean, my room was clean and cute&amp;ndash; for a dorm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life this week..</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_21/</guid>
      <description>Time to recap the life portion of the school life balance from last week!
Monday at the gym ALL OF THE DUMBBELLS WERE THERE. I have never seen this before. People suck at picking up after themselves&amp;hellip;
Tuesday night we grilled on the roof. We were hoping to catch some Tennis up there on the TV- but apparently our complex has different subscriptions in different rooms.. So after, we ended up back in the apartment subscribing to tennis channel&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w5</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_18/</guid>
      <description>Wow, what a week! It seriously FLEW by. First, I&amp;rsquo;ll review some pictures from the week, then get into the nitty gritty of projects&amp;hellip;.
After the weekend, I decided that Monday was the best day to bring Rex into class. It works for our schedule, and fits better with the general flow at school. He only stayed a half day- because, projects. Also, HE SHAMED THE FAMILY by deciding to mark a classmates bag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring is close...</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_12/</guid>
      <description>Energy was pretty low this week, and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t feeling fantastic some days- but it was a good week.
Monday night we rented Dr. Strange. IT WAS SO GOOD. It&amp;rsquo;s actually probably one of my favorite movies now. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to own it and watch it again and again&amp;hellip; I HOPE there is another (&amp;amp;soon).
Tuesday was my early day so we hit the gym and took it easy.
Wednesday Zac and I grabbed lunch at Brider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w4</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_11/</guid>
      <description>Monday morning two classmates pulled together to bring in a BUNCH of doughnuts! They are for sure not on the plan- but I had one and it literally made me happy- so there&amp;rsquo;s that. (ps. they were awesome for doing that).
We started off the week with a guest speaker- a UX designer! It was a really interesting talk- and I appreciate seeing and hearing from different people in the tech field- who work in the various aspects of web development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack the Planet</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_06/</guid>
      <description>HACK THE PLANET WAS SO MUCH FUN.
So Saturday I participated in my FIRST EVER HACKATHON. It was also the first ever gSchool hackathon. The event started around 8:30, but I showed up early to get put into a team. Since I&amp;rsquo;m still new to this world, and the event wanted to encourage cross cohort/location collaboration- I decided to go in as a single and get paired up with a group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another week goes by!</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_05/</guid>
      <description>SO MANY PHOTOS IN THIS POST&amp;hellip;
Last Sunday was a prepare for the week day! Steph and Geoff had just left on Saturday, so I spend Sunday catching up around the house, grabbing groceries, and mostly meal prepping!
We stopped at the container store, and Zac ensured that I contained myself. Still my fav.
Monday night was craft night! I headed over to Cojo&amp;rsquo;s with my banner supplies for Stephs Shower!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w3</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_03_04/</guid>
      <description>Week three of module one is officially complete! At the end of the week, I am feeling pretty great!
Monday we covered objects, arrays and intro to jQuery. I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t looked at objects in months.. and for sure needed a refresher. I liked learning jQuery&amp;mdash; although I know to be careful in using it for all things in the future.
This week we had Roberto as our floating instructor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VISITORS</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_25/</guid>
      <description>Saturday morning we cleaned up around the house- then headed to the airport to meet Steph &amp;amp; Geoff!
Luckily, Steph brought supplies to restock our Wegmans necessities! the best!
We were so excited to have guests, and there were so many places we wanted to take them!
Saturday evening we headed over to Galvanize, so I could show all three around my new school. We met an instructor and one of my cohort peers who was getting some work in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w2</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_24/</guid>
      <description>A short week! Monday we were off for Presidents day! Tuesday we started off covering test based assessments. Right now, we are using them for some of our assessments- but I look forward to Q2 when we learn how to write them! Now we have an updated flow/map of Q1:
We also spent some more time on Responsive CSS. I will say that by the end of this week, I feel much better about the topic and like flex box a lot more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Balance</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_18/</guid>
      <description>So this past week was my first at Galvanize, but there was time outside of class! I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to break up my posts between school work, and life outside of class..
This past week Zac was in Portland, so every night we caught up on my day! I think he was as excited as me that I started school.
Monday I came home and just relaxed. All week it was really great that I had easy meals ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwd46 m1w1</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_17/</guid>
      <description>WEEK ONE GALVANIZE!
On day one, we played the name game Mighty Michelle and met instructors, administrators, etc! Our first lesson was on &amp;lsquo;How to learn.&amp;rsquo; They served us a great lunch- wraps from protein bar!
My legs were super sore from runday on Sunday, and standing through the name game killed me! So, I sat on the ground. Nothing like a first impression-
In the afternoon, we got another tour, received our key fobs and talked about the Galvanize Culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful weekend</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_12/</guid>
      <description>Last free weekend before Galvanize was wonderful! Thursday evening I headed over to Galvanize for an informal get together- saying HI before starting on Monday. I met Kiki, our class dog!
Thursday night we headed out to Avanti for dinner. It was a gorgeous night, and we stopped by Prost first.
It was so nice to sit outside and chat about life. Then we headed to Avanti, we sat downstairs, ordered some pizza for National pizza day, and went up to the roof for a little while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A busy relaxing week</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_08/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been so gorgeous here lately, that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that a week ago everything was covered in ice! We had a nice day, and right as the sun was setting, starting getting some drizzle. Well, it all turned to ice and our walk that night and the next morning was treacherous.
I am officially in the last week of the January 2017 Tone It Up Challenge! I&amp;rsquo;m loving it, and I plan to keep it up afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>659 Square Feet</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_05/</guid>
      <description>Back in July we moved out of our house in NY. It was a 1,452 sqft house (not including the full finished basement, or the bonus room above the garage). We moved from a house with four bedrooms, and two bathrooms to a one bed, one bath apartment. A mere 659 sqft. Here, my friends, is how we make it work..
FULL DISCLOSURE: We also have a storage unit. It&amp;rsquo;s small, and contains our spare tires, tool box and bikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitness &amp; Friends</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_02_01/</guid>
      <description>Friday night we went out for Thai! As usual, Zac ordered the better dish. Mine was a little (way) too spicy for my likes, so I helped Z out a bit. It was good, but we&amp;rsquo;ll still be on the hunt for Denvers best Thai!
Saturday night we went out for a few drinks. We wanted to stay close, since Zac was still recovering. We headed to Zengo, but they had a huge Year of the Rooster celebration going on, and we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to get in the door!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sick &amp; sick.</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_27/</guid>
      <description>Last week Rex and I had some movie dates. We watched The Secret Life of Pets (adorable) and The Legend of Tarzan (amazing). I even let him on the couch, because I. Am. Weak.
We had a few beautiful days, so we went on long walks in the highlands and lodo.
Zac got home last Thursday night, and he has been sick with an awful cold since.
Then, this weekend, Rex got some form of conjunctivitis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Catchup</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_26/</guid>
      <description>Since moving to Denver in July, I have been working hard to learn how to code.
Way back in middle school, I ran a website. It was for quotes- which I am sure were not properly cited, but the site was cool, the cursor had a tail, and it was definitely pink. I was self taught. After school, I would come home and sit at the computer for hours trying to figure out how the code worked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight Gone Bad</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_19/</guid>
      <description>It takes 21 days to make a habit, and I&amp;rsquo;m on day 19 of Tone It Up! That&amp;rsquo;s 2 days from a habit? AND 2 days since &amp;ldquo;Ditch Day&amp;rdquo;. This week I&amp;rsquo;m feeling great again. Last week I had some ups and downs-
First, helpful tool of the week: CARDIO PLAYLIST ON SPOTIFY. Seriously love this list so much. After I finished my last audiobook, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get into the next one I picked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The movies, Lax and drinks!!</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_17/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s only been 9 days since my last post, and I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s been 9 days! After a slow start to last week, the second half and weekend flew by! I think this post will be a long one&amp;hellip;
(How great is that sweatshirt thought? It&amp;rsquo;s IndyBrand and I want ALL THE THINGS).
Monday morning Zac was off to LA for work! Rex and I went for a great walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tone it Up!</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_10/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been just over a week since I started Tone It Up! I&amp;rsquo;ve used the nutrition plan for Fit Girls a few times the past couple years, and while I loved the food, I started to get sick of the same recipes. It was time to switch things up!
So far, I&amp;rsquo;m loving the meals- and the daily workouts are definitely doable.
One dinner I love is Lentil Butternut Squash Soup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting off 2017!</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_08/</guid>
      <description>Hope everyone has had a great start to the year! It was a cold week here in Denver, but we had a great week nonetheless. I have been re-watching Downton Abbey&amp;ndash; on Monday I realized I could stream Amazon Video through the XBox, and I am THRILLED. Truth is, I missed the last season, and I need to watch! I&amp;rsquo;ve kept them playing pretty much all day while I work on different CodeAcademy/Computer Projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Reads</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_05/</guid>
      <description>In December I finished 11 books. That&amp;rsquo;s CRAZY! I think that I associate the holiday season with curling up with a book.. and therefore take every opportunity to do so!
The books: The Graveyard Book Vol 1,
The Graveyard Book Vol 2,
Winter Stroll, Winter Storms, Eligible, Crooked Kingdom, The Woman in Cabin 10, All The Time in the World, A Man Called Ove, Paper Princess
Thoughts:
The Graveyard Book by Neil Gaiman, and Craig P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Travel</title>
      <link>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 12:19:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.mihshhehl.com/blog/2017_01_01/</guid>
      <description>It has been a crazy week, but it was full of family, friends and ended with the start of the New Year!
On Christmas Eve we drove up to Rochester to see my Aunt and cousins. My Aunt throws a &amp;ldquo;Chrismukkah&amp;rdquo; party, and her best friend brings her two adorable girls, her husband, and their parents. It was great to see them all again- to practice my lazy ASL and get an insight to RSL (The grandparents speak RSL and know hardly any ASL!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>