<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>food on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/categories/food/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in food on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://libmb.github.io/categories/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight Gone Bad</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It takes 21 days to make a habit, and I&amp;rsquo;m on day 19 of Tone It Up! That&amp;rsquo;s 2 days from a habit? AND 2 days since &amp;ldquo;Ditch Day&amp;rdquo;. This week I&amp;rsquo;m feeling great again. Last week I had some ups and downs-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_spotify.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;playlist&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, helpful tool of the week: CARDIO PLAYLIST ON SPOTIFY.
Seriously love this list so much. After I finished my last audiobook, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get into the next one I picked. I was only a few days away from a new Audible credit, so I decided to wait it out and listen to some music (&amp;amp; catch some TV like NFL GAME DAY and a movie here or there). I have my new credit, and love my new book- but I only listen to it during cardio. Ironically, the rest of the time, I&amp;rsquo;m moving to the Cardio Playlist! If you&amp;rsquo;re into high octane music, give it a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_tv.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tv&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I learned last week is that I NEED TO EAT. I was so busy- I was jumping from one thing to the next and not prioritizing all 5 meals. So, I&amp;rsquo;d skip one, or two, in a day. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t feel hungry, until bed time. At that point, I knew I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to eat anything. I&amp;rsquo;m trying REALLY hard not to eat anything after 7pm. So, I went to bed hungry. This was a HUGE MISTAKE. With the workouts, cardio and yoga I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing- I need food! Power! Energy! (Also, everyone needs food, and you should never go to bed hungry). I ended up crashing last week- and took some long naps. Then I started keeping up with meals. Even if I had to combine a M2 and M3, or a M4 and M5. I ate all the food in the plan. And you know what- I didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed hungry, and I have so much energy. So, EAT! It&amp;rsquo;s part of taking care of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_food.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eating aside, I also somehow hurt my leg this past weekend. Just a strained muscle- but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to move it into an injury- so while I&amp;rsquo;ve kept up on all workouts, I have been going just a little bit easier on my cardio (little less resistance, a few less strides/minute). It already feels better and I think I&amp;rsquo;ll kick cardio back up a notch in a day or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym window&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for workouts, I never purchased the workout videos from Tone It Up. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;ve been creating my own circuits. The ability to create these, well, I give all of the credit to Crossfit! Oh- a 22 minute video doing legs and shoulders? I&amp;rsquo;ll throw together an EMOM. Or a METCON. Or, my absolute fav, Fight Gone Bad Style. Today there was an Arms and Abs video I don&amp;rsquo;t have- so I threw together this FGB style workout: crunches, plank, sit ups, push ups, arm circles, break, dumbbell side bend, med ball chopper, farm carry, balance point crunches, break. The flow feels really productive- and you can do anything for 1 minute!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_FGB.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;workout&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Crossfit- I do miss it. I miss it most on days when the plan calls for something like deadlifts, and I&amp;rsquo;m like- where my Olympic Weights at? Haha. I can only do so much with 12 lb dumbbells&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took a little time off from Yoga this week- due to my leg, but I did make one great class on a sunny morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;yoga&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight, Zac gets home- and he&amp;rsquo;s off travel next week. I&amp;rsquo;ll be happy to have my work out partner back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_bud.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Zac&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Midway through week 4, I love the plan. My water intake is 100% and my eating is great. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_day.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;day&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>