<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coffee on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/categories/coffee/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coffee on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://libmb.github.io/categories/coffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Sick &amp; sick.</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_27/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week Rex and I had some movie dates. We watched The Secret Life of Pets (adorable) and The Legend of Tarzan (amazing). I even let him on the couch, because I. Am. Weak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/secretlife.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;movie&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a few beautiful days, so we went on long walks in the highlands and lodo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/highlands.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;highlands&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/lodo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lodo&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac got home last Thursday night, and he has been sick with an awful cold since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/siczac.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;zac&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, this weekend, Rex got some form of conjunctivitis. So, with a ton of medicine and as much patience as possible, I have been caring for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/sick.png&#34; alt=&#34;zac and rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Rogue order came in on Friday! It has been so helpful! The sklz slidez are great- I kept falling off my other ones. These have grooves which allow greater movement without losing your place! The ab mat is fantastic, and I grabbed the shirt for Zac (it fits with his general philosophy and when I saw it I couldn&amp;rsquo;t pass it ups).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/fitness.png&#34; alt=&#34;rogue&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend, I made moroccan stew. It&amp;rsquo;s not my favorite dish, but I&amp;rsquo;m also not use to sweet tasting soups. I LOVED Chia seed pudding. A great way to satisfy a sweet tooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/food.png&#34; alt=&#34;food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lately, I have had an addiction to Lattes. Seriously, I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed. I don&amp;rsquo;t even like the taste of coffee any more- I am totally ruined. We have two great places within walking distance: Ink &amp;amp; Carbon. At Ink, I love the white almond latte. At Carbon, I always switch it up. They make their own syrups, and I always love what I get. This week I grabbed a lemon verbena and it was amazing. I&amp;rsquo;ve been researching options for making them at home&amp;hellip; but no clear solution yet. &lt;em&gt;sighs.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/latte.png&#34; alt=&#34;latte&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday, was football day. UGH. What an anxiety filled game. Rex settled his head right on our legs, probably trying to ground us. It was a night full of cuss words and &amp;ldquo;Oh Man&amp;rdquo; texts to my brother. I went to bed totally heartbroken. I still love my team, and I look forward to seeing them next season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/steelers.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;steelers&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting up early has been harder this week&amp;hellip; but when I manage to get myself up and moving, I am greeted by a wonderful sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/sunrise.png&#34; alt=&#34;morning&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This weekend will probably be low-key, but next week Zac will be in LA, and I have some fun things planned to pass the time. Two weeks until school!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>