<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fitness on Shelter&#39;s House</title>
    <link>https://libmb.github.io/categories/fitness/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in fitness on Shelter&#39;s House</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://libmb.github.io/categories/fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Balance</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So this past week was my first at Galvanize, but there was time outside of class! I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to break up my posts between school work, and life outside of class..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This past week Zac was in Portland, so every night we caught up on my day! I think he was as excited as me that I started school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday I came home and just relaxed. All week it was really great that I had easy meals ready to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/mondinner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuesday was Valentines day! Rex got a treat of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/rexvday.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Valentines&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Galvanize, I headed to the gym. A very nice lady decided to talk to me while I was on the elliptical. She was concerned that I was at the gym alone (also the only person in the gym) on Valentines. I explained that Zac was in Portland- but come on- who does that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/vdaygym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After going to the gym and talking to Zac, Rex and I watched some Twilight while working on some CLI Murder Mystery! It was a really fun way to practice command line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/vdayfun.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;CLI&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wednesday my new bag came! I ordered an everyday tote- it is awesome! It has all of these collapsable dividers and is the perfect size. I love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/bag.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Peak Design Everyday Tote&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the CodePen Meetup, I headed to the gym at Galvanize. It was totally empty, and it was nice to change up the scenery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/ggym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday night Zac got home from Portland (and will be home for three weeks at least!!). I immediately had him run through a Git/Github exercise to explain some concepts for me. He&amp;rsquo;s a sweet guy..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/zacgit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;git hub&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All week I stopped home for Rex at lunch. All week he would watch me eat before heading to the dog park. He pretty much moped- I think he misses all our fun weekday adventures- but we&amp;rsquo;ll make it up on the weekends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/lunchrex.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rexy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The meal planning/prepping was lifesaving. It was the only reason I had time this week! AND, this week I had grapefruit as M2. I realized it has been 10 years since I had a grapefruit, and I LOVE THEM. So, I need to eat those more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/lunch.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;prepped lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/grapefruit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Grapefruit&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a really great week. The weather was nice, and it felt good to be busy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_18/weather.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;weather&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful weekend</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last free weekend before Galvanize was wonderful! Thursday evening I headed over to Galvanize for an informal get together- saying HI before starting on Monday. I met Kiki, our class dog!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/kiki.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Kiki the dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thursday night we headed out to Avanti for dinner. It was a gorgeous night, and we stopped by Prost first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/prost.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Beer and City&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was so nice to sit outside and chat about life. Then we headed to Avanti, we sat downstairs, ordered some pizza for National pizza day, and went up to the roof for a little while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/avanti.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Avanti&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday I spent a bunch of time sitting outside with Rex. It was really nice out, and that way Zac has some privacy during his work calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/outside.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Patio view&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent hours meal planning for the entire first module of Galvanize ( !4 weeks worth! )- The module is five weeks long, but we will have company the first week so it didn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to plan a bunch of meals when we&amp;rsquo;ll probably play the week by ear. Anyways, I was super impressed with my work. 4 weeks worth of 5 tone it up meals a day, complete with shopping lists and meal prep schedules. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s gorgeous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/mealplan.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Computer screen&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday we went out for dinner again. Monday starts the tone it up seven day slim down- I hadn&amp;rsquo;t grabbed groceries yet- so it was a good opportunity to get out again. ALSO it was high 70s and we wanted to enjoy a patio! We went to Larimer and stopped at a wine bar. We did two wine tastings and enjoyed some appetizers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/larzac.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Zac at Larimer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/larimer.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Larimer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way home we stopped for coffee. Because love for coffee &amp;gt; shouldn&amp;rsquo;t drink coffee at night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/amante.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Amante Coffee&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we relaxed all day- caught up on some house stuff. Sunday morning I headed out for my hair appointment. Since moving to Denver i&amp;rsquo;ve been going to Clementines in the highlands. On Sunday they opened a new location in Stapleton, and my hairdresser will be working there from now on! I decided to go there- to keep her, and check out the new place. It was really nice, I ended up being the first customer at the new location on opening day. It&amp;rsquo;s located at Stanley Marketplace, this awesome old airplane hangar that has been converted to shops and restaurants/breweries. There was a crossfit place that looked awesome too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/clementines.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Clementines&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way out, I grabbed two lattes from Logan&amp;rsquo;s Coffee House. They were great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/logans.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;coffee&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday evening was meal plan time! I threw on the 90s playlist from Spotify, and got to work. Throughout I was snapping the process. I know that I snapped more to my story that day than I have ever before, combined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/mealprep.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;meal preping&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/shoes.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;shoes&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt so good afterwards! 5 days of quality meals. As for fitness, my new shoes came in this week- and I had some really great workouts. It was nice to have Zac home all week again. It&amp;rsquo;s always great to have a gym buddy. We did some biking together&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/bike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_12/gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A busy relaxing week</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been so gorgeous here lately, that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that a week ago everything was covered in ice! We had a nice day, and right as the sun was setting, starting getting some drizzle. Well, it all turned to ice and our walk that night and the next morning was treacherous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/cold.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ice outside&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am officially in the last week of the January 2017 Tone It Up Challenge! I&amp;rsquo;m loving it, and I plan to keep it up afterwards. I&amp;rsquo;ve been really sore this past week, but a good sore!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/tiu.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;fitness challenge&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I jumped on the bike this week, to change up my cardio routine. I need to get some practice in before summer! I want to be in shape so I can keep up with my new biking friends (and, as always, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to keep up with my husband). Personally, I still think assisted downhill is the. way. to. go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/bike.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;indoor bike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we headed to Eldora! It was a gorgeous day- the snow was amazing. I just love it! We took ZERO indoor breaks on Saturday. The best part was eating lunch on my favorite run. We&amp;rsquo;re still working our way through my last batch of chili. I&amp;rsquo;ll need to make more before Steph and Geoff come it visit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/eldoracol.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;eldora lunch&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/eldoraz.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;zac at Eldora&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got home in the afternoon, the sun was still up and it was 60 degrees! We took the pup downtown, and stopped at Panera to grab some bread for the week. They were out of our favorite loaf, so we decided to try some Asiago. It was good, but, the other is better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/panera.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;panera&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday night we watched Man in the High Castle, and enjoyed some wine and cheese. On that note, we actually caught up this week. We have so many questions! It&amp;rsquo;s such a good show, and the characters are great, but some things just don&amp;rsquo;t make sense! I guess that&amp;rsquo;s how they get you to keep watching&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/cheese.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rex begging&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday we decided to take Rex on an adventure. We had been gone most of Saturday, and we wanted to give him a chance to get out some energy! I looked at some of the hikes I had highlighted last year, and decided to head to Mt. Falcon. It&amp;rsquo;s only 30 minutes away, and it claimed to have awesome views of red rocks and Denver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/mtfalconz2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Take a Hike&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a gorgeous day, and for the first half of our hike, we were actually pretty warm. Then, on the way back, we hit the dark side of the trails, and found ourselves trudging through snow!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/sunsnow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mt Falcon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hike was as described, and had awesome views to take in. There was a lookout tower you could climb up, and this awesome little pavilion that is set right on the edge. I told Zac, it gave me serious window view goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/falconviews.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Views from Mt Falcon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was our first hike of 2017. Rex had the BEST. DAY. EVER. And we had a great time too. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to get back out more often. It&amp;rsquo;s really rejuvenating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/mtfalconm.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Me at Mt Falcon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/mtfalconz.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sign&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday I had to run some errands, and got caught in a massive slow down on the 25. It was like a parking lot. I have no patience for slow traffic, and driving standard makes it worse. I was pretty much done when I got home, so I went straight to the gym to take out my frustrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/parkinglot.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Slow down on 25&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday night we went out for groceries, but I forgot my reusable shopping bags. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious, Ikea bags will do in a pinch- haha.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/ikea.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Groceries&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week has been filled in with working on precourse work for Galvanize. I CANT wait to start on Monday. I&amp;rsquo;m probably going to go in later this week to meet instructors and jazz. I finished most of the assignments, and set up all my accounts, so it feels real!  AND late last week I got awesome news, that I received a scholarship! It pretty much made my day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/gschool.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gSchool&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I got the itch to re-arrange our furniture. I knew that if I didn&amp;rsquo;t do it now, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have time! SO- while Zac was busy working, I set to moving all our belongings around him. He usually hates it when I move things- it gives him anxiety until it&amp;rsquo;s finished. However, he was a total champ. I&amp;rsquo;ll post a picture of the new layout next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/move.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Furniture moving&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As it is, I have a few more goals before Monday. 1. Make chili 2. Meal plan like CRAZY (5 weeks worth?) 3. Keep up with my daily reading goals- because I so want to finish this Epic Fantasy within my month goal and 4. SIT IN THE SUN AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_08/sunshine.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sun&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitness &amp; Friends</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_02_01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Friday night we went out for Thai! As usual, Zac ordered the better dish. Mine was a little (way) too spicy for my likes, so I helped Z out a bit. It was good, but we&amp;rsquo;ll still be on the hunt for Denvers best Thai!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/thai.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dinner&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday night we went out for a few drinks. We wanted to stay close, since Zac was still recovering. We headed to Zengo, but they had a huge Year of the Rooster celebration going on, and we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to get in the door! So we went next door to McLoughlins. It was probably for the better. They were playing great 90s music and had the X Games on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/drinks.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drinks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Australian Open was on at 1 am, so we (Zac) were determined to stay up for it! Rafa and Fed? It was sure to be a great match, and from what I&amp;rsquo;ve heard, it was! I fell asleep as soon as it started. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t stay up another minute! Zac was a champ and watched the whole thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/aus.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tennis&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday Zac was super tired from his late night so we pretty much just hung out and watched The Man at the High Castle. I went to the gym, of course. The workouts are still great, and this week they&amp;rsquo;re amping them up a little. It&amp;rsquo;s great timing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/fitness.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made omelettes for breakfast with the veggies I had left over from the week. We also tried the Ginger Sesame Chicken from TIU and it was fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/food.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday I took Rex on some errands. During the weeks while Zac is gone I try to take Rex everywhere. It helps keep his energy down! Monday I rewarded him with a quick stop at Krisers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/errands.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dog&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Amazon order came in Monday afternoon. Two more of the BEST sports bras, and a new container of ACV. I spent the afternoon meal prepping. I made Almond Butter cookies for the cookie smoothie on the plan this week. Its delicious! I also made some Cinnamon Energy Bites to take to craft night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/drink.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;drinks&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before leaving for the evening, I took Rex for a nice long walk. We got some really good views of the sunset. I do wish I could grab a photo that does the mountains justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/sunset.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;sunset&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Monday I grabbed a lyft to Cojos for Craft Night! I missed the last few months due to holiday travel, and I&amp;rsquo;m so excited I finally made it. Ladies, wine, food, crafts. What else could you want in an evening? I even managed to organize someones prismacolor pencils. Because, personality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ALSO BTW. Lyft/Uber rides are my favorite thing since moving to Denver. Really. Someday I&amp;rsquo;ll give a little rave for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/craft.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;craft&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I cleaned up and took a bunch of photos for my next blog post. I also caught up on The Vampire Diaries. Zac&amp;rsquo;s sister, Mel, and I are the hugest TVD Fans. This week when NINA posted that she&amp;rsquo;d be coming back- we pretty much freaked out. I AM SO EXCITED.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_02/2017_02_01/tvd.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tvd&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I have some precourse work to start for gSchool&amp;hellip;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sick &amp; sick.</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_27/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week Rex and I had some movie dates. We watched The Secret Life of Pets (adorable) and The Legend of Tarzan (amazing). I even let him on the couch, because I. Am. Weak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/secretlife.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;movie&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a few beautiful days, so we went on long walks in the highlands and lodo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/highlands.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;highlands&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/lodo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;lodo&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac got home last Thursday night, and he has been sick with an awful cold since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/siczac.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;zac&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, this weekend, Rex got some form of conjunctivitis. So, with a ton of medicine and as much patience as possible, I have been caring for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/sick.png&#34; alt=&#34;zac and rex&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Rogue order came in on Friday! It has been so helpful! The sklz slidez are great- I kept falling off my other ones. These have grooves which allow greater movement without losing your place! The ab mat is fantastic, and I grabbed the shirt for Zac (it fits with his general philosophy and when I saw it I couldn&amp;rsquo;t pass it ups).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/fitness.png&#34; alt=&#34;rogue&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend, I made moroccan stew. It&amp;rsquo;s not my favorite dish, but I&amp;rsquo;m also not use to sweet tasting soups. I LOVED Chia seed pudding. A great way to satisfy a sweet tooth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/food.png&#34; alt=&#34;food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lately, I have had an addiction to Lattes. Seriously, I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed. I don&amp;rsquo;t even like the taste of coffee any more- I am totally ruined. We have two great places within walking distance: Ink &amp;amp; Carbon. At Ink, I love the white almond latte. At Carbon, I always switch it up. They make their own syrups, and I always love what I get. This week I grabbed a lemon verbena and it was amazing. I&amp;rsquo;ve been researching options for making them at home&amp;hellip; but no clear solution yet. &lt;em&gt;sighs.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/latte.png&#34; alt=&#34;latte&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunday, was football day. UGH. What an anxiety filled game. Rex settled his head right on our legs, probably trying to ground us. It was a night full of cuss words and &amp;ldquo;Oh Man&amp;rdquo; texts to my brother. I went to bed totally heartbroken. I still love my team, and I look forward to seeing them next season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/steelers.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;steelers&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting up early has been harder this week&amp;hellip; but when I manage to get myself up and moving, I am greeted by a wonderful sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_27/sunrise.png&#34; alt=&#34;morning&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This weekend will probably be low-key, but next week Zac will be in LA, and I have some fun things planned to pass the time. Two weeks until school!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight Gone Bad</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It takes 21 days to make a habit, and I&amp;rsquo;m on day 19 of Tone It Up! That&amp;rsquo;s 2 days from a habit? AND 2 days since &amp;ldquo;Ditch Day&amp;rdquo;. This week I&amp;rsquo;m feeling great again. Last week I had some ups and downs-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_spotify.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;playlist&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, helpful tool of the week: CARDIO PLAYLIST ON SPOTIFY.
Seriously love this list so much. After I finished my last audiobook, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get into the next one I picked. I was only a few days away from a new Audible credit, so I decided to wait it out and listen to some music (&amp;amp; catch some TV like NFL GAME DAY and a movie here or there). I have my new credit, and love my new book- but I only listen to it during cardio. Ironically, the rest of the time, I&amp;rsquo;m moving to the Cardio Playlist! If you&amp;rsquo;re into high octane music, give it a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_tv.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;tv&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I learned last week is that I NEED TO EAT. I was so busy- I was jumping from one thing to the next and not prioritizing all 5 meals. So, I&amp;rsquo;d skip one, or two, in a day. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t feel hungry, until bed time. At that point, I knew I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to eat anything. I&amp;rsquo;m trying REALLY hard not to eat anything after 7pm. So, I went to bed hungry. This was a HUGE MISTAKE. With the workouts, cardio and yoga I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing- I need food! Power! Energy! (Also, everyone needs food, and you should never go to bed hungry). I ended up crashing last week- and took some long naps. Then I started keeping up with meals. Even if I had to combine a M2 and M3, or a M4 and M5. I ate all the food in the plan. And you know what- I didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed hungry, and I have so much energy. So, EAT! It&amp;rsquo;s part of taking care of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_food.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;food&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eating aside, I also somehow hurt my leg this past weekend. Just a strained muscle- but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to move it into an injury- so while I&amp;rsquo;ve kept up on all workouts, I have been going just a little bit easier on my cardio (little less resistance, a few less strides/minute). It already feels better and I think I&amp;rsquo;ll kick cardio back up a notch in a day or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym window&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for workouts, I never purchased the workout videos from Tone It Up. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;ve been creating my own circuits. The ability to create these, well, I give all of the credit to Crossfit! Oh- a 22 minute video doing legs and shoulders? I&amp;rsquo;ll throw together an EMOM. Or a METCON. Or, my absolute fav, Fight Gone Bad Style. Today there was an Arms and Abs video I don&amp;rsquo;t have- so I threw together this FGB style workout: crunches, plank, sit ups, push ups, arm circles, break, dumbbell side bend, med ball chopper, farm carry, balance point crunches, break. The flow feels really productive- and you can do anything for 1 minute!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_FGB.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;workout&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Crossfit- I do miss it. I miss it most on days when the plan calls for something like deadlifts, and I&amp;rsquo;m like- where my Olympic Weights at? Haha. I can only do so much with 12 lb dumbbells&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took a little time off from Yoga this week- due to my leg, but I did make one great class on a sunny morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;yoga&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonight, Zac gets home- and he&amp;rsquo;s off travel next week. I&amp;rsquo;ll be happy to have my work out partner back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_bud.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Zac&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Midway through week 4, I love the plan. My water intake is 100% and my eating is great. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_19/2017_01_19_day.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;day&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tone it Up!</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been just over a week since I started Tone It Up! I&amp;rsquo;ve used the nutrition plan for Fit Girls a few times the past couple years, and while I loved the food, I started to get sick of the same recipes. It was time to switch things up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, I&amp;rsquo;m loving the meals- and the daily workouts are definitely doable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One dinner I love is Lentil Butternut Squash Soup. I really did not think I would enjoy this.. but I really like everything about it. It has just the right amount of spice and texture. I actually already made it a second time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_bns.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also finally tried smoothie bowls. The first time, I used a fresh banana because I hadn&amp;rsquo;t had time to freeze them yet- and without realizing the difference it makes, I was really confused as to why people make smoothie bowls. I actually just grabbed a straw to drink it. The next day, I decided to try again, and the frozen banana made all the difference. I LOVE this breakfast. It&amp;rsquo;s almost as great as eating frozen yogurt with great toppings. Almost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_bowl.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zac and I have been hitting the gym on his lunch break. It&amp;rsquo;s so great to have a gym partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_gym.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;gym&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A serious goal for 2017 is to improve my double unders. I mean, I only string together a max of 6, so there is a lot of room for improvement. Until then, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep beating myself up. Literally, whip marks on my legs, arms and sometimes I&amp;rsquo;ll need to ice a knuckle or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_rope.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;double&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every workout has been followed by a smoothie.. and I love, love, LOVE smoothies. I drink mine in like 2 minutes, while Zac takes a while- you know, drinking at a normal pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_smoothie.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;smoothie&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, Kindness Yoga is also holding a January Challenge. My goal is to get to 15 classes this month. I went to 4 classes last week, and they make such a huge difference in how I feel. It&amp;rsquo;s been hard- I prioritize it after my workout for the day, and sometimes I can hardly hold myself up because my muscles are so tired. Still worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_10/2017_01_10_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;soup&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting off 2017!</title>
      <link>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libmb.github.io/post/2017_01_08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hope everyone has had a great start to the year! It was a cold week here in Denver, but we had a great week nonetheless. I have been re-watching Downton Abbey&amp;ndash; on Monday I realized I could stream Amazon Video through the XBox, and I am THRILLED. Truth is, I missed the last season, and I need to watch! I&amp;rsquo;ve kept them playing pretty much all day while I work on different CodeAcademy/Computer Projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_comp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;downton&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of computer projects&amp;mdash; on Wednesday I lured a friend out for drinks so that I could question her about WebDev and local programs. She was an awesome source of information (as well as an awesome person)- and I have a lot to consider. Wednesday this coming week I am attending an info session at Turing School, and then I&amp;rsquo;ll start applying and see what happens. It might take a few tries, but I am loving everything I&amp;rsquo;m learning, and I am ready to move forward at a faster pace!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday night we went to the Botanic Gardens for an Off The Clock event. The same friend above invited us, and we meet another couple there. It was a fun little night. I just LOVE walking around the gardens. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for summer- I think I&amp;rsquo;ll just go and sit a couple days a week- because. It also makes me wish I could grow things, but let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, keeping plants alive is not my strong suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_gardens.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday we were planning on snowboarding, but were just too sore to make it up. Instead, we slept in and took care of some things around the apartment. In the morning, we walked to Panera Bread to get a loaf (and a Caramel Latte) to go with our bean-less Chili. I made a large batch in December and froze portions for trips to the mountain. I had already thawed one, so chili for lunch it was! Rexy loved the walk- and he gets more compliments, laughs and smiles when he wears his boots. Seriously, no one is immune to the cuteness that is dog boots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_panera.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Panera&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got home, it was straight to the paw-wash! Of course, he was filthy, and overjoyed by the prospect of being hosed down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_dogbath.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday afternoon I finished up another jar of Justin&amp;rsquo;s Almond Butter. I have been drinking SO MANY smoothies, and eating so many smoothie bowls, that I needed a cost effective option. I mentioned this to Zac, and an hour later, he was in the kitchen whipping up a batch of his first ever homemade PB! Guys- ITS AMAZING. Now, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for peanuts we can buy in bulk&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_pb.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sunday, it was FOOTBALL DAY. How about them Steelers? Gosh I am so excited about this post season. After the Steelers game, I headed to the gym- where I caught most of the Packers Giants game, and the Golden Globes Red Carpet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_elip.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;TV&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it was time for Restorative Yoga at Kindness. I love this weekly class- its the perfect way to wrap up a week! It was a particularly great class- and afterwards, Zac met me with Rex to walk home. Always the gentleman, he carries my Yoga mat like a pro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_yoga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t believe it&amp;rsquo;s 2017 already. I will say, that being back in Denver finally feels like home and not just a vacation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://libmb.github.io/images/2017_01/2017_01_08/2017_01_08_denver.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Gardens&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>